<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogsia</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Blogsia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor><webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>All Answers To Sophronia Franklin Quiz In Hogwarts Legacy</title><link>/post/all-answers-to-sophronia-franklin-quiz-in-hogwarts-legacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/all-answers-to-sophronia-franklin-quiz-in-hogwarts-legacy/</guid><description>Hogwarts Legacy is a sweet love letter to the dedicated Potterheads or the fans of the Wizarding World around different Muggles. But jokes aside, this game allows you to interact with several NPC characters during your academic fifth year in Hogwarts. One of these includes Sophronia Franklin who whilst being two years younger can outsmart you. It can also be vice-versa if you don’t mind some trivia questions about the Potterverse.</description></item><item><title>Anime Pet Simulator Codes (February 2023)</title><link>/post/anime-pet-simulator-codes-february-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/anime-pet-simulator-codes-february-2023/</guid><description>Are you searching for the latest Roblox Anime Pet Simulator codes? This is where you can find them all in one place. Keep scrolling to also find out how to redeem these codes and listed out the expired codes, if any.
Anime Pet Simulator is where you can collect the most powerful Anime heroes, explore worlds and work towards becoming the best player ever. Thankfully, there are codes available which will help you in your adventure.</description></item><item><title>Cookie Run OvenBreak Characters Explained</title><link>/post/cookie-run-ovenbreak-characters-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/cookie-run-ovenbreak-characters-explained/</guid><description>Since launching in 2016, Cookie Run OvenBreak has amassed a huge player base thanks to its varied and unique gameplay mechanics. But the real stars of the show are the over 170 playable characters, each with a distinct look and attitude (not to mention cute). We felt like we need to list them all out as a tribute to the now 6-year game and so we did! Here are all the playable (sorry Hello kitty and Mimmy) Cookie Run OvenBreak characters for you to enjoy.</description></item><item><title>How To Make Golden Pets in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-make-golden-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-make-golden-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is about collecting Pets, getting coins and diamonds, and upgrading pets. With every upgraded pet, their stats increase. The first upgrade for the pets in the game is golden pets. Golden pets have three times more stats than normal pets. If you are curious about how to get Golden Pets in Pet Simulator X then read this article till the end.
How to get Golden Pets in Pet Simulator X?</description></item><item><title>How To Quickly Get Fantasy Coins In Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-quickly-get-fantasy-coins-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-quickly-get-fantasy-coins-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>You can use Fantasy Coins to buy exciting items in Roblox Pet Simulator X, making it a very desirable currency. In this article, we will show you how to get these coins quickly.
How to Get Fantasy Coins Fast in Roblox Pet Simulator X? Check out the different ways you can get Fantasy Coins quickly in Roblox Pet Sim X.
Triple Fantasy Coins Boost in Pet Simulator X Yes, that’s right.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Lankybox Simulator Codes (March 2023) – Get Free Coins</title><link>/post/roblox-lankybox-simulator-codes-march-2023-get-free-coins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-lankybox-simulator-codes-march-2023-get-free-coins/</guid><description>Are you seeking the most up-to-date Roblox Lankybox Simulator codes? Don’t worry, you’ve come to the correct place. We’ll go over all of the active codes today, as well as how to use them. This page also includes a list of expired codes for your convenience.
These codes are working as of March 8, 2023, when we checked. But Roblox codes tend to expire in 2 to 3 days. We will be updating new codes as they are released.</description></item><item><title>Adopt Me Trading Values List (March 2023)</title><link>/post/adopt-me-trading-values-list-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/adopt-me-trading-values-list-march-2023/</guid><description>This Adopt Me Pet Trading Value List will give you a valuable list of all the Legendary, Ultra Rare, Rare, Uncommon, and Common pets. This list will help you get the best value exchange for your pets and collect those hard-to-get pets. This list is courtesy of u/Hennessyxy, who has given full details like each pet’s Normal, Neon, and Mega values. OP has made a lot of effort to make this list and update it.</description></item><item><title>How To Equip More Pets?</title><link>/post/how-to-equip-more-pets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-equip-more-pets/</guid><description>If you are new to Roblox Pet Simulator X, you may have come across players who have loads of pets and wondered how they could equip them. Since the game revolves around collecting different pets and progressing through several islands and biomes, you too will want to know how you can get more pets. In this article, we will show you how you can do so.
How to Equip More Pets in Roblox Pet Simulator X?</description></item><item><title>How To Find &amp;amp; Unlock The Forsaken Gate In Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-find-unlock-the-forsaken-gate-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-find-unlock-the-forsaken-gate-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>If you play Roblox Pet Simulator X, you may have spotted the mysterious-looking Forsaken Gate. This gate is located behind the egg shop, and it is known to be guarding a secret egg. In this article, we will show you how to search and open this gate in the game.
How to Unlock The Forsaken Gate in Roblox Pet Simulator X? If you want to get the Forsaken Gate in Roblox Pet Sim X, keep reading the steps below:</description></item><item><title>How To Get &amp;amp; Use Boosts In Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-use-boosts-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-use-boosts-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is a Roblox game where you collect resources like Coins &amp;amp; Diamonds to get and Hatch Pet Eggs. With these Pets, you can get more Coins and repeat the process. The end goal of Pet Simulator X is to be the number 1 player on the Leaderboard. Well, how do you get on top of the Leaderboard? It’s pretty simple actually, all you need to do is grind with your Pets to get more Coins.</description></item><item><title>How To Get A Rainbow Samurai Dragon In Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-a-rainbow-samurai-dragon-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-a-rainbow-samurai-dragon-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>The Rainbow Samurai Dragon is one of the best pets you can find in Roblox Pet Simulator X. In this article, we will show you how you can get your hands on this rare pet.
How to Get a Rainbow Samurai Dragon in Roblox Pet Simulator X? If you want to know how you can get a Rainbow Samurai Dragon in Roblox Pet Simulator X, keep reading the steps in this article.</description></item><item><title>How To Get Good Pets In Pet Simulator X?</title><link>/post/how-to-get-good-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-good-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Getting good pets in Pet Simulator X helps enhance the experience of what is already quite an interesting game. Having the best pets in the game will allow you to progress further more quickly, while also enabling you to earn bigger amounts of money and rewards. However, as you read these lines, you’re probably wondering, how can you get your hands on these pets in the first place? Well, the answer is simple, and that’s exactly what we will explain in this guide, so keep reading to learn how to acquire good pets in Pet Sim X.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X: How to Make Dark Matter Pets</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-make-dark-matter-pets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-make-dark-matter-pets/</guid><description>Pets are everything in Pet Simulator X. If you’re interested in having a fun time while getting some of the coolest pets ever, this is the game for you. One of the newest additions to the game is Dark Matter Pets that you can now create in the game. In this guide, we will show you how to convert and make your own Dark Matter pets in the popular Roblox game, Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Simulators With Pets And Trading: 10 Best Experiences</title><link>/post/roblox-simulators-with-pets-and-trading-10-best-experiences/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-simulators-with-pets-and-trading-10-best-experiences/</guid><description>There are various Roblox Simulators that allow you to interact with pets and engage in trading. Roblox Experiences try to emulate real life as much as possible. These games have been pretty popular with many players across various age groups. Hence, we have managed to compile a list of the 10 best pet simulator games that you can play. Let’s find out more!
Roblox Pets and Trading Simulators: 10 Best Experiences Pet Store Tycoon Pet Store Tycoon is one of the most wholesome games that you can take part in.</description></item><item><title>What Happened To Pet Simulator X (Content Deleted)?</title><link>/post/what-happened-to-pet-simulator-x-content-deleted/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/what-happened-to-pet-simulator-x-content-deleted/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is one of the most popular Roblox games ever made. At the time of writing, it had 252,081 active users and 3.7B+ visits, which is huge. This fame is well-deserved because the game is awesome and super engaging. But something strange happened in March 2022 and if you’re wondering what happened to Pet Simulator X and why did it say ‘Content Deleted’, here are the details.
What Happened to Pet Simulator X – Did it get Deleted?</description></item><item><title>Best Ways To Get Pets In Pet Simulator X Via Trading</title><link>/post/best-ways-to-get-pets-in-pet-simulator-x-via-trading/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/best-ways-to-get-pets-in-pet-simulator-x-via-trading/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is one of the most popular games on Roblox right now. And the aspect that many players love is trading. While there are events that may require you to unlock and hatch special eggs, some might be obtained via trading. If you are confused about how to make this happen, here’s how to get pets in Pet Sim X via trading.
How to Get Pets in Pet Simulator X via Trading?</description></item><item><title>How To Dupe Pets In Pet Sim X 2022 (Pet Simulator X)?</title><link>/post/how-to-dupe-pets-in-pet-sim-x-2022-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-dupe-pets-in-pet-sim-x-2022-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>The Pet Sim X glitch to duplicate pets dupe is back. Many players have mentioned this on Twitter and a lot of players are trying to implement it in this game. So let’s look at what we actually know about how to dupe pets in Pet Sim X (Pet Simulator X) in 2022.
How to Duplicate in Pet Simulator X (Pet Sim X Pets Dupe) in 2022? Currently, the only way to duplicate pets in Pet Simulator X (Pet Sim X Dupe) is by downloading a krnl script from Pastebin and running it through a hack script.</description></item><item><title>How To Get Diamonds Or Gems In Pet Simulator X Fast</title><link>/post/how-to-get-diamonds-or-gems-in-pet-simulator-x-fast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-diamonds-or-gems-in-pet-simulator-x-fast/</guid><description>Diamonds are a currency that you need to earn slowly and steadily in this game. You will be able to see how many Diamonds you have on the right side of the screen. But how to get Diamonds or Gems fast in Pet Simulator X? There are a few ways to speed up your process. Let’s find out more about these methods and also how to use this currency.
How to Get Diamonds in Pet Simulator X Quickly The fastest ways to get diamonds are by using codes, trading and buying them from the Exclusive Shop.</description></item><item><title>How To Get Dominus Egg &amp;amp; ALL Epic Dominus Pets</title><link>/post/how-to-get-dominus-egg-all-epic-dominus-pets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-dominus-egg-all-epic-dominus-pets/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X or Pet Sim X allows players to upgrade and even fuse pets together to get new pets. But getting any type of Dominus pet seems to be one of the most difficult tasks in the game. So if you are wondering how to get all Dominus pets with Dominus Egg in Pet Simulator X, here’s how to do this.
How to Unlock &amp;amp; Get Dominus Egg in Pet Simulator X?</description></item><item><title>How To Get More Halloween Candy In Pet Sim X FAST?</title><link>/post/how-to-get-more-halloween-candy-in-pet-sim-x-fast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-more-halloween-candy-in-pet-sim-x-fast/</guid><description>The much-loved Roblox game Pet Simulator X gets a Halloween update/makeover and through it, you can obtain lots of candies. In this guide, we will show you all the possible ways to get candy in Pet Sim X fast!
How to Get More Candy in Pet Simulator X (Fast) These are the different methods to get Halloween Candy in Pet Sim X pretty quickly:
Get it from the big chests in different worlds.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X: How To Get Pogchamp Achievement</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-get-pogchamp-achievement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-get-pogchamp-achievement/</guid><description>Getting Pogchamp Achievement in Roblox Pet Simulator X / Pet Sim X seems like an impossible task. If you also feel so, don’t worry you are on the right path. This achievement is still one of the mysteries in the gaming world. So today let’s look at this achievement.
How to Get Pogchamp Achievement in Pet Sim X / Pet Simulator X? To get Pogchamp Achievement in Pet Simulator X or Pet Sim X, you need to spend 25 Billion Fantasy Coin to unlock the Tech area, and also get a Poggers Cat pet (PogCat).</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X: How To Unlock &amp;amp; Fuse Pets</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-unlock-fuse-pets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-unlock-fuse-pets/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X or Pet Sim X allows players to upgrade and even fuse pets together to get new pets. Even though this information is available on the Roblox page of the game, many players are not sure how to do this. So today we will look at how to unlock and fuse pets in Pet Simulator X or Pet Sim X.
How to Unlock and Fuse Pets in Pet Simulator X or Pet Sim X?</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X: List Of All Pets And Eggs</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-list-of-all-pets-and-eggs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-list-of-all-pets-and-eggs/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X, a game where you collect gold and diamonds to unlock pets and from multiple tiers of eggs. Higher the tier of an egg, the better the pet. The pets can range from the cutest Bunnies to the fiercest Dragons and the most majestic Unicorns. It can be confusing to remember all of the pets so here is a list of all the Pets and Eggs in Roblox Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>What Time Does The Mystery Merchant Spawn In Pet Simulator X?</title><link>/post/what-time-does-the-mystery-merchant-spawn-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/what-time-does-the-mystery-merchant-spawn-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Mystery Merchant is a new merchant in Pet Simulator X. It works in ways similar to Traveling Merchant, in a sense that both sell pets. The main difference between them is that Mystery Merchant sells pets a lot cheaper. Although, that also makes it spawn less frequently. So in this guide let us take a look at the spawn times and locations of Mystery Merchant in Pet Simulator X and also learn about the Traveling Merchant.</description></item><item><title>Best Discord Servers Links For Trading In Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/best-discord-servers-links-for-trading-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/best-discord-servers-links-for-trading-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is one of the most played games on Roblox. One of the most fascinating elements of this game is obtaining new Pets. Besides using the Use the Trading Plaza feature, one
can Trade Pets with other players. The only thing required is another player who is also ready to trade. The world is big and it may be difficult for you to find such players. Don’t
worry, as this guide features some of the Best Discord Servers for Trading in Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>Fart Simulator Codes Roblox (March 2023) - NEW</title><link>/post/fart-simulator-codes-roblox-march-2023-new/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/fart-simulator-codes-roblox-march-2023-new/</guid><description>Looking for Fart Simulator codes for Roblox in February 2023? If so then you have come to the right place. Some of these codes might expire. So, make sure you bookmark this page and redeem this code. So let’s find out all the new codes for this game.
Roblox Fart Simulator Codes These codes have been updated and are correct at the time of publishing. If you use the given codes you will get some free rewards such as jewels and pets!</description></item><item><title>How To Get Into Tech World In Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-into-tech-world-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-into-tech-world-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X consists of various Worlds and Biomes to explore. Tech World is add on to the world. This world consists of many exciting features such as Dark Tech Biome or Dark Matter Pets. If you are curious to know how to unlock Tech World in Pet Simulator X then this guide will help you.
How to Unlock Tech World in Pet Simulator X The first and foremost step to unlock Tech World is to unlock all Biomes in Spawn World, especially Glacier Biome.</description></item><item><title>How To Trade In Pet Simulator X (Explained)</title><link>/post/how-to-trade-in-pet-simulator-x-explained/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-trade-in-pet-simulator-x-explained/</guid><description>Trading is a crucial part of Pet Sim X. When you trade pets, you can get the chance to get a Pet that you’ve been wanting for a while. Through this method, you can even obtain Legendary pets and some Diamonds or Gold as well. If you are confused about how to trade in Pet Simulator X, this quick guide will help you with the entire process.
How to Trade in Pet Simulator (Sim) X?</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Enchantments Wiki List</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-enchantments-wiki-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-enchantments-wiki-list/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X has a special way to improve the stats of any of your pets by applying Enchats by using a method called Enchantment. These enchantments are powers or abilities that make your pet better in the way you want. There are some pets who already come with these enchants. So today we will look at everything you need to know about all enchants in our Enchantments Wiki list.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Merch Codes (April 2023)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-merch-codes-april-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-merch-codes-april-2023/</guid><description>Many users are wondering how to get the new Huge Cat from the Pet Simulator X Merch Codes. So today we will look at all about these codes and the new exclusive pet, along with the pet stats and more. So without any further ado let’s jump right into it.
What are the Merch Codes for Pet Simulator X? The Pet Simulator X Merch Codes or merchant codes are unique codes just for everyone who bought real-life “Cat Plush” from Big Games Online Store.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Pets Value List (April 2023)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-pets-value-list-april-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-pets-value-list-april-2023/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is a Roblox game that involves collecting and purchasing a plethora of pets. As you progress, you will gather plenty of coins and gems to buy them. With these purchased pets, you can trade them to earn plenty of riches. That being said, you need to know the value of these pets before you do so. Not to worry, here’s the value list for all the pets in Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X: How To Get Huge Pets</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-get-huge-pets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-how-to-get-huge-pets/</guid><description>Huge Pets are a thing of fascination for a lot of players to get in Pet Sim. But they are really hard to come by and moreover, many players are not sure about how to obtain them. So today we will find out how to get Huge Pets like Cat, Cupcake, Dragon, Huge Dog, and more in Pet Simulator X (Pet Sim).
How to Get Huge Pets in Pet Simulator X Here are all the Huge Pets in Pet Simulator X:</description></item><item><title>Roblox Pet Simulator X Ranks Explained</title><link>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-ranks-explained/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-ranks-explained/</guid><description>Ranking in Pet Simulator X can be tricky to understand at the start. Relax, I am going to share a lot of details on how really the Pet Simulator X Tier system work. What will be your base rank as you start and how to level up to rank in Pet Simulator X. It is a Roblox game where you can grab coins and diamonds to buy eggs. These eggs hatch into cute or sometimes scary pets.</description></item><item><title>All enchantments in Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/all-enchantments-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/all-enchantments-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is the latest game in the Pet Simulator series, promising more pets than you could ever handle in real life and all the challenges and benefits that come with that territory. However, to make the most of your pets, you’re going to need to apply enchantments to them. This guide covers every enchantment in the game and what they all do. For those who don’t know, enchantments used to be applied randomly to pets, and you couldn’t acquire them any other way.</description></item><item><title>How to fuse pets in Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-fuse-pets-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-fuse-pets-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X players will get access to the option to fuse pets after they unlock the game’s third area, the Beach. This will cost 75,000 coins, so players will need to spend some time farming those up first. The fusion area can be found on the right side of the start of the Beach, players will be able to see a sign that says “Fuse Pets”. To fuse pets, players will need at least three pets, although it is possible to fuse up to twelve different pets at once.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Despacito Egg in Roblox - Despacitegg</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-despacito-egg-in-roblox-despacitegg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-despacito-egg-in-roblox-despacitegg/</guid><description>The Roblox Egg Hunt is upon us, which means over 50 different eggs have been hidden in various Roblox games. The Descpacito Egg, or Despacitegg, can be found in the game Robloxian High School.
Just type Robloxian High School into the search bar, and you will be able to click the play button to join the game. You will start in a house, so leave, look around, then head for the center of town.</description></item><item><title>How to use the Huge-A-Tron in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-use-the-huge-a-tron-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-use-the-huge-a-tron-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Huge Pet variants in Roblox Pet Simulator X are hands down the best Pets you can obtain in the game, and the Huge-A-Tron is a convenient means that allows you to create a Huge Pet whenever you wish. Typically, Huge Pets are tied to BIG Games Shop merchandise, limited-time seasonal events, or extremely rare Egg drops, such as the Huge Balloon Cat from the Royal Egg. You also have a slight chance of acquiring a Huge Machine Egg from enrolling your Pets at the Daycare for six-hour durations.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Codes Wiki (March 2023)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-codes-wiki-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-codes-wiki-march-2023/</guid><description>Our Roblox Pet Simulator (Sim) X Codes page includes the most recent list of active OP codes including the latest updates, that can be redeemed for a large number of free Diamonds, Pets and more. Today, we’ll go over all of them and how to redeem and use them as well. We’ve also included a list of expired codes on this page for your reference.
Also Read: Pet Simulator X “Merch” Codes</description></item><item><title>Roblox Egg Simulator codes (December 2022)</title><link>/post/roblox-egg-simulator-codes-december-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-egg-simulator-codes-december-2022/</guid><description>Egg Simulator has likely risen to fame thanks to the number of pets you are able to collect. Although you could earn most through games and currency, the best way to go about doing so is through entering each of the promotional codes. How to redeem codes in Egg Simulator In any server you are in, there will be a twitter logo plastered on the left side of your screen. There, you will enter each code.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Pet Simulator 3 codes (February 2023)</title><link>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-3-codes-february-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-3-codes-february-2023/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator 3 is a fan-made version of the popular game Pet Simulator X, which allows players to adopt and care for various cute and cuddly pets, ranging from cats and dogs to mythical creatures such as unicorns and dragons. The game’s objective is to ensure that your pets remain happy and healthy.
One of the unique features of Roblox Pet Simulator 3 that sets it apart from other pet simulation games is the fact that it gives you infinite money, gems, and everything else you need.</description></item><item><title>What does "Ad hoc enim estis carnales" mean in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/what-does-ad-hoc-enim-estis-carnales-mean-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/what-does-ad-hoc-enim-estis-carnales-mean-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is a relatively family-friendly game where players get to collect amazingly cute animals and use them to make money and diamonds. These resources are then used to get even more animals that you will love to collect. However, at the start of the game, in the spawn area, there is a huge door with a lock over it. If you interact with this locked gate, the game will give you a message that says “Ad hoc enim estis carnales.</description></item><item><title>Where is the Auction in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/where-is-the-auction-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/where-is-the-auction-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>One of the main features added to Roblox Pet Simulator X during the February 2023 update is the Auction Board, a giant billboard that lets Pet Owners bid on each other’s ultra-rare Pets for Diamonds. The main appeal of this mechanic is that it allows players to cooperate on single transactions as a mass group rather than forming nonformal circles in the Trading Plaza and spamming the chat with their offers.</description></item><item><title>All pets in Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/all-pets-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/all-pets-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>In Roblox Pet Simulator X, your main goal is to gather coins so you can purchase eggs that work as loot boxes for the game. Each egg has a chance to hatch one of the multiple pets that are available at that rarity. Of course, the more coins you get, the better egg you can purchase. Here are all of the available eggs and what animals hatch from them in Roblox Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>How to get a legendary egg in Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-a-legendary-egg-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-a-legendary-egg-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is a Roblox game where you can collect a variety of pets. Pets can be obtained in a number of ways, such as trading in coins which can be obtained by playing the game normally or redeeming codes. The different pets you collect in the game can vary from being basic to legendary, the rarest but most valuable kind of pet you can get. Legendary pets are also the strongest and fastest in the game, so they’re definitely worth seeking out.</description></item><item><title>How to get diamonds fast in Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-diamonds-fast-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-diamonds-fast-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>In Roblox Pet Simulator X, diamonds are very important. It’s a resource that you will need to try and earn all the time, as it will allow you to buy important items and even trade with other players.
In this guide, we will break down some basic ways to earn diamonds, and a simple trick to get them faster. To increase the number of diamonds you get in the game, you will want to make your way to the Upgrade machine.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Pog Cat in Roblox Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-pog-cat-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-pog-cat-in-roblox-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>The recent update in Roblox Pet Simulator X saw the addition of PogWorld. This includes the addition of PogWorld achievement and the infamous Pog Cat. For players trying to obtain the latest pet, here’s how you can do it.
How to get the Pog Cat To get Pog Cat in Roblox Pet Simulator X, follow the below-mentioned steps:
Head to the spawn island, which is the location for purchasing eggs in the game.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X value list – the highest value pets</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-the-highest-value-pets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-the-highest-value-pets/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X is a Roblox game that, as the name suggests, allows you to buy and raise adorable pets. Some of these are typical pets, like dogs and cats, while others are more outlandish, like dragons, wolves, and demons. Many players earn in-game currency by raising and then selling their pets, but you want to make sure you get a good price for your effort. If you’re looking for the pets that will give you the most money when you sell them, here are the highest-value pets in Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Pet Simulator X codes (November 2022)</title><link>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-codes-november-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-codes-november-2022/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is the latest and greatest game in the Pet Simulator series. If you want to own more pets than you know what to do with, then this is the perfect game for you. However, we all like a little help in our games, which is why we’ve put together this list of all known Roblox Pet Simulator X codes.
How to redeem Roblox Pet Simulator X codes Launch Roblox Pet Simulator XPress the Pet button at the bottom of the screenClick the star icon at the bottom of the screenScroll down until you find the Redeem Codes option and click on itType in the code you wish to redeemConfirm the code and the reward will be redeemed to your accountWorking Roblox Pet Simulator X codes The following is a list of all the codes we know to be working in Roblox Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>Anime Monkey Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/anime-monkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/anime-monkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>32nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Anime Monkey is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Anime Update. It hatches from the Exclusive Anime Egg at a 20% chance.
The Anime Monkey has a current starting value around 3B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Elf Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/elf-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/elf-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>22nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Elf Cat is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained from opening the Christmas 2022 Stocking. It has a 49% chance to hatch from the Christmas Stocking.
The Elf Cat has a current starting value around 961.1M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Hubert Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/hubert-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/hubert-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>16th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET Hubert is an Exclusive pet that is only available to developers &amp;amp; partners of Big Games. If you want one you have to pay a high price!
The Hubert has a current starting value around 1T gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Floppa Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-floppa-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-floppa-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>241st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET Huge Floppa is an Exclusive pet from the Summer 2022 mini-update as a 35% chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Huge Floppa has a current starting value around 70B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Gargoyle Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-gargoyle-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-gargoyle-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Gargoyle Dragon is an Exclusive pet from the Axolotl Oceans update as a 2% chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Huge Gargoyle Dragon has a current starting value around 120B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Jolly Penguin Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-jolly-penguin-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-jolly-penguin-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>69th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Jolly Penguin is an Exclusive huge pet that was added with the Christmas 2022 update. It could have been hatched from the Snowman Egg and the Golden Snowman Egg.
The Huge Jolly Penguin has a current starting value around 30B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Santa Paws Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-santa-paws-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-santa-paws-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>158th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Santa Paws is a Limited / Exclusive pet that came with the Christmas 2021 update. It could have been hatched from the Insane Christmas Egg at a .5% chance.
The Huge Santa Paws has a current starting value around 200B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Pixel Wolf Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/pixel-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pixel-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>155th most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The Pixel Wolf is a Legendary pet that was added with the Pixel World update &amp;amp; can be hatched from the Rainbow Pixel Egg.
The Pixel Wolf has a current starting value around 5M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Punkey Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/punkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/punkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>40th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET Punkey is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; can currently be purchased for 1,199 Robux.
The Punkey has a current starting value around 20B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Techno Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/techno-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/techno-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The Techno Cat is a Legendary pet that can be hatched from the Dark Tech Egg. It is a re-skin of the regular Cat.
The Techno Cat has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Hell Chest Mimic Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/hell-chest-mimic-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/hell-chest-mimic-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>204th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Hell Chest Mimic is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Hell update &amp;amp; cost 500 Robux.
The Hell Chest Mimic has a current starting value around 97B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Capybara Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-capybara-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-capybara-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>153rd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Capybara is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Hardcore/Anniversary update on July 29th, 2022. It could be hatched from the Exclusive Capybara Egg at a 1.5% chance.
The Huge Capybara has a current starting value around 50B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Grim Reaper Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-grim-reaper-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-grim-reaper-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>251st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Grim Reaper is an Exclusive pet released with the Halloween 2022 Event update. It could be hatched from the Cursed Egg at a ?%
The Huge Grim Reaper has a current starting value around 140B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Monkey Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-monkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-monkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>244th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Monkey is a Huge Exclusive pet that can be redeemed with a code that comes with the purchase of the Huge Monkey plushy. The Huge Monkey is a re-skin of the regular Monkey which can be hatched from the Wood Egg. There is no value for this pet yet, check back soon.
The Huge Monkey has a current starting value around 80B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Present Mimic Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-present-mimic-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-present-mimic-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>231st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Present Mimic is an Exclusive huge pet that was added with the Christmas 2022 update part 2. It can be hatched from the Present Egg at a 0.7% chance.
The Huge Present Mimic has a current starting value around 100B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Scary Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-scary-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-scary-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>156th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Scary Cat is an Exclusive pet released with the Halloween 2022 Event update. It could be obtained from the Halloween Gift as a 1% chance.
The Huge Scary Cat has a current starting value around 30B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Pog Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/pog-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pog-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>191st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Pog Dragon is a Limited edition pet that can no longer be obtained. To get this pet you had to say Knock Knock at the blue door &amp;amp; hatch POG Eggs.
The Pog Dragon has a current starting value around 6B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Scary Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/scary-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/scary-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>7th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Scary Cat is an Exclusive pet released with the Halloween 2022 Event update. It could be obtained from the Halloween Gift as a 49% chance.
The Scary Cat has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Wicked Empyrean Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/wicked-empyrean-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/wicked-empyrean-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>189th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Wicked Empyrean Dragon is an Exclusive pet from the Glitch update as a 13% chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Wicked Empyrean Dragon has a current starting value around 16B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>A 36 Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/a-36-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/a-36-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>177th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The A-36 is a Mythical pet that can be hatched from the Titanium Egg.
The A 36 has a current starting value around 195M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Alien Parasite Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/alien-parasite-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/alien-parasite-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>219th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Alien Parasite is a Mythical pet that can be hatched from the Martian Egg located in the Alien Forest.
The Alien Parasite has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Chest Mimic Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-chest-mimic-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-chest-mimic-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>157th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Chest Mimic is an Exclusive pet that could be obtained from the Season 1 Gifts DLC in pet sim x.
The Huge Chest Mimic has a current starting value around 325B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Forest Wyvern Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-forest-wyvern-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-forest-wyvern-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>243rd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Forest Wyvern is an Exclusive pet from the hacker portal update as a 2% chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Huge Forest Wyvern has a current starting value around 82.2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Lucky Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/lucky-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/lucky-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>119th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Lucky Cat was added in the Mastery Update as a 13% chance from the Robux Exclusive Egg.
The Lucky Cat has a current starting value around 10.2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Otter Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/otter-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/otter-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>58th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Otter is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 599 Robux.
The Otter has a current starting value around 11B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Party Pig Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/party-pig-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/party-pig-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>118th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Party Pig is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Anime Update. It hatches from the Update Hype Gift at a 15% chance.
The Party Pig has a current starting value around 966.8M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Rave Crab Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/rave-crab-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/rave-crab-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>114th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Rave Crab was added in the Mastery Update as a 50% chance from the Robux Exclusive Egg.
The Rave Crab has a current starting value around 5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Sapphire Phoenix Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/sapphire-phoenix-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sapphire-phoenix-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>99th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Sapphire Phoenix is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; can currently be purchased for 5,999 Robux.
The Sapphire Phoenix has a current starting value around 35B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Anniversary Gift Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/anniversary-gift-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/anniversary-gift-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>95th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Anniversary Gift was a limited edition gift box that was given for free to all players who were ranked Pro or higher on the day of the anniversary event. It can be opened for a change to hatch a Party Cat or Huge Party cat. You can also trade the gift itself.
The Anniversary Gift has a current starting value around 4B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Guest Noob Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/guest-noob-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/guest-noob-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>162nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Guest Noob is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Fantasy update &amp;amp; could be purchased for 600 Robux.
The Guest Noob has a current starting value around 109.8B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Lovemelon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-lovemelon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-lovemelon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>Suggest Values for Huge Lovemelon You can only make one suggestion per type every 24 hours</description></item><item><title>Nebula Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/nebula-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/nebula-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Nebula Dragon is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Tech update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 5,199 Robux.
The Nebula Dragon has a current starting value around 600B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Party Dog Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/party-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/party-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>10th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Party Dog is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Anime Update. It hatches from the Update Hype Gift at a 80% chance.
The Party Dog has a current starting value around 877.7M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Pegasus Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/pegasus-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pegasus-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The Pegasus is a Legendary pet that can be hatched from the Heaven Egg.
The Pegasus has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Turkey Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/turkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/turkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>179th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Turkey is a Mythical pet that was added with the Autumn 2022 Event. It could be hatched from the Acorn Egg &amp;amp; the Diamond Acorn Egg.
The Turkey has a current starting value around 525M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Wyvern Of Hades Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/wyvern-of-hades-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/wyvern-of-hades-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>185th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Wyvern of Hades is a Mythical pet that can be hatched from the Hell egg at around a .000067% chance. It is a remodel of the Ghoul Horse.
The Wyvern Of Hades has a current starting value around 3B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Easter Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/easter-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/easter-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>254th most popular pet today
BASIC PET The Easter Cat is a Basic pet that was released with the Easter 2022 event &amp;amp; could be hatched from basic blue eggs that were scattered around the map.
The Easter Cat has a current starting value around 500M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Elf Dog Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/elf-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/elf-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>75th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Elf Dog is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained from opening the Christmas 2022 Stocking. It has a 49% chance to hatch from the Christmas Stocking.
The Elf Dog has a current starting value around 950M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Galaxy Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/galaxy-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/galaxy-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>151st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Galaxy Dragon is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Fantasy Update &amp;amp; could be purchased for 4,500 Robux.
The Galaxy Dragon has a current starting value around 61B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Galaxy Pegasus Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/galaxy-pegasus-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/galaxy-pegasus-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Galaxy Pegasus is an Exclusive pet that could be purchased from the shop for 5,199 Robux.
The Galaxy Pegasus has a current starting value around 234B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Crystal Dog Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-crystal-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-crystal-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>162nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Crystal Dog is an Exclusive pet that could be obtained from the Season 1 Gifts DLC in pet sim x.
The Huge Crystal Dog has a current starting value around 105B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Sapphire Phoenix Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-sapphire-phoenix-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-sapphire-phoenix-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>112th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Sapphire Phoenix is an Exclusive pet that could be obtained from the Season 1 Gifts DLC in pet sim x.
The Huge Sapphire Phoenix has a current starting value around 230B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Skeleton Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-skeleton-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-skeleton-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>287th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Skeleton is an unconfirmed Exclusive pet that is though to be obtainable from the newest wave of PSX DLC gifts.
The Huge Skeleton has a current starting value around 100B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Mosaic Corgi Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/mosaic-corgi-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/mosaic-corgi-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>97th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Mosaic Corgi is an Exclusive pet that could be obtained from the Season 1 Gifts DLC in pet sim x.
The Mosaic Corgi has a current starting value around 10B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Sock Corgi Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/sock-corgi-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sock-corgi-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>161st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Sock Corgi is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Alien update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 1,299 Robux.
The Sock Corgi has a current starting value around 19.2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Astral Axolotl Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/astral-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/astral-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>163rd most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The Astral Axolotl is a Legendary pet that came with the Axolotl Ocean update. It can be hatched from the Shiny Axolotl Egg.
The Astral Axolotl has a current starting value around 300M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Fairy Queen Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/fairy-queen-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/fairy-queen-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>124th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Fairy Queen is an Exclusive pet from the Axolotl Oceans update as a 13% chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Fairy Queen has a current starting value around 7.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Glitched Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/glitched-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/glitched-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>243rd most popular pet today
BASIC PET The Glitched Cat is a Basic pet that came with the hacker portal update. It can be hatched from the Glitch Egg with a 49% chance.
The Glitched Cat has a current starting value around 160M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Hacked Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/hacked-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/hacked-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
RARE PET The Hacked Cat is a Rare pet that came with the hacker portal update. It can be hatched from the Hacker Egg with a 5% hatch chance.
The Hacked Cat has a current starting value around 100M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Koala Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/koala-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/koala-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>93rd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Koala is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Pixel World update &amp;amp; can be hatched from the Exclusive Pets Egg at a 50% chance.
The Koala has a current starting value around 6B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Pog Dog Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/pog-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pog-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>210th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Pog Dog is a Limited edition pet that can no longer be obtained. To get this pet you had to say Knock Knock at the blue door &amp;amp; hatch POG Eggs.
The Pog Dog has a current starting value around 11.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Pony Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/pony-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pony-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>30th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Pony is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Pixel World update &amp;amp; can be hatched from the Exclusive Pets Egg at a 35% chance.
The Pony has a current starting value around 4B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Silver Stag Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/silver-stag-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/silver-stag-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Silver Stag is a Mythical pet that came with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; hatched from the Egg of Many Gifts.
The Silver Stag has a current starting value around 2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Sock Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/sock-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sock-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>205th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Sock Cat is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Bank update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 1,299 Robux.
The Sock Cat has a current starting value around 22.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Empyrean Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/empyrean-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/empyrean-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The Empyrean Dragon is a Legendary pet that can be hatched from the Empyrean Egg at around a .035% chance.
The Empyrean Dragon has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Hc Turkey Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/hc-turkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/hc-turkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The HC Turkey is a hardcore Mythical pet in the PSX "Autumn 2022 update! It is the hardcore version of the Turkey.
The Hc Turkey has a current starting value around 1.1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Lucki Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-lucki-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-lucki-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>232nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET Huge Lucki is an Exclusive pet that was added with the "Lucky Block" update. This pet can only be hatched from the Lucky Eggs which are a rare random drop from Lucky Blocks.
The Huge Lucki has a current starting value around 130B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Mrs Paws Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-mrs-paws-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-mrs-paws-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET Huge Mrs. Paws is an Exclusive huge pet that was added with the Christmas 2022 update part 2. It could have been hatched from the Gold Snowman Egg.
The Huge Mrs Paws has a current starting value around 70B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Lava Scorpion Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/lava-scorpion-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/lava-scorpion-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>134th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Lava Scorpion is an Exclusive pet that could be purchased from the shop for 599 Robux. Only available from trading.
The Lava Scorpion has a current starting value around 25B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Nyan Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/nyan-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/nyan-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>100th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET Nyan Cat is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Tech update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 1,299 Robux.
The Nyan Cat has a current starting value around 69.4B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Phantom Wolf Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/phantom-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/phantom-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>179th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Phantom Wolf is a Mythical pet that can be hatched from the Haunted Egg at around a .0075% chance.
The Phantom Wolf has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Sad Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/sad-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sad-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>169th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET Sad Cat is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Steampunk update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 1,299 Robux.
The Sad Cat has a current starting value around 100B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Silver Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/silver-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/silver-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>166th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Silver Dragon is a Mythical pet that came with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; hatched from the Egg of Many Gifts.
The Silver Dragon has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Blue Big Maskot Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/blue-big-maskot-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/blue-big-maskot-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>8th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Blue Big Maskot is a super Exclusive pet that can only be obtained by purchasing Preston's avatar items &amp;amp; completing the Dress Up achievement.
The Blue Big Maskot has a current starting value around 105B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Galaxy Fox Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/galaxy-fox-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/galaxy-fox-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Galaxy Fox is a Mythical pet that can can be hatched from the Planet Egg at around a .00044% chance.
The Galaxy Fox has a current starting value around 500M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Ghoul Horse Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/ghoul-horse-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/ghoul-horse-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>52nd most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Ghoul Horse is a Limited / Mythical pet that can be hatched from both the Eerie &amp;amp; Cursed Eggs at around a .0003% chance.
The Ghoul Horse has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Grumpy Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/grumpy-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/grumpy-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>95th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Grumpy Cat is an Exclusive pet that could be purchased from the shop for 499 Robux. Can only be obtained by trading.
The Grumpy Cat has a current starting value around 50B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Ducky Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-ducky-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-ducky-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Ducky is an Exclusive DLC pet which came with the purchase of the PSX Huge Ducky plush. It cost $49.99 when it was for sale on BigGames website.
The Huge Ducky has a current starting value around 170B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Lucky Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-lucky-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-lucky-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>233rd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Lucky Cat was added in the Mastery Update as a 2% chance from the Robux Exclusive Egg.
The Huge Lucky Cat has a current starting value around 80B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Sea Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/sea-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sea-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>200th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Sea Dragon is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Bank update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 599 Robux.
The Sea Dragon has a current starting value around 12.2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>The Easter Bunny Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/the-easter-bunny-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/the-easter-bunny-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>209th most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The Easter Bunny is a Legendary pet that was released with the Easter 2022 event &amp;amp; could be hatched from Legendary orange eggs that spawned randomly around the map every 30 minutes.
The The Easter Bunny has a current starting value around 2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Titanic Jolly Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/titanic-jolly-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/titanic-jolly-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>33rd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Titan Jolly Cat is an Exlusive Titanic pet that was added with the Christmas 2022 part 2 update. It is the very first Titanic pet in the game. You can click to mount &amp;amp; ride the titanic pets.
The Titanic Jolly Cat has a current starting value around 1T gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Capybara Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/capybara-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/capybara-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>47th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Capybara is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Hardcore/Anniversary update on July 29th, 2022. It could be hatched from the Exclusive Capybara Egg at a 50% chance.
The Capybara has a current starting value around 2.8B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive Egg Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/exclusive-egg-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/exclusive-egg-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>74th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Exclusive Egg is an Exclusive item that can be purchased for Robux in Pet Sim X. You can now choose to hatch the egg or trade it to another player.
The Exclusive Egg has a current starting value around 11.8B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Festive Elf Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/festive-elf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/festive-elf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>246th most popular pet today
RARE PET The Festive Elf is a Rare pet that came with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; hatched from the Christmas Tree Egg (3%) &amp;amp; Egg of Many Gifts (80%).
The Festive Elf has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Gargoyle Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/gargoyle-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/gargoyle-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>72nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Gargoyle Dragon is an Exclusive pet from the Axolotl Oceans update as a chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Gargoyle Dragon has a current starting value around 6B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Axolotl Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>153rd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Axolotl is a Huge Exclusive pet that can be redeemed with a code that comes with the purchase of the Huge Axolotl plushy. The Huge Axolotl is a re-skin of the regular Axolotl which can be hatched from the Samurai Egg. There is no value for this pet yet, check back soon.
The Huge Axolotl has a current starting value around 112B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Pixel Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-pixel-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pixel-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>273rd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Pixel Cat is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Pixel World update &amp;amp; can be hatched from the Rainbow Pixel Egg.
The Huge Pixel Cat has a current starting value around 37.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Party Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/party-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/party-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>105th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Party Dragon is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Anime Update. It hatches from the Update Hype Gift at a 5% chance.
The Party Dragon has a current starting value around 980M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Rich Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/rich-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/rich-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>111th most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The Rich Cat is a Legendary pet that was released with the Pet Sim X "Cat World" update. It can be hatched from the Yarn and Cat Eggs.
The Rich Cat has a current starting value around 50M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Storm Wolf Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/storm-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/storm-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>187th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Storm Wolf is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Alien update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 4,999 Robux.
The Storm Wolf has a current starting value around 70B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Christmas 2022 Stocking Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/christmas-2022-stocking-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/christmas-2022-stocking-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>106th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Christmas 2022 Stocking is a gift that you can get when you claim a DLC code from a PSX toy or plushy. The only way to get this Stocking is to purchase a DLC item or trade for it from another player.
The Christmas 2022 Stocking has a current starting value around 21B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Dominus Astra Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/dominus-astra-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/dominus-astra-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>77th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Dominus Astra is an Exclusive pet that was available to purchase on release day for 5,000 Robux.
The Dominus Astra has a current starting value around 200B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Hellish Axolotl Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/hellish-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/hellish-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>146th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Hellish Axolotl is a Mythical pet that came with the Axolotl Ocean update. It can be hatched from the Shiny Axolotl Egg.
The Hellish Axolotl has a current starting value around 300M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Pumpkin Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-pumpkin-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pumpkin-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>170th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Pumpkin Cat is a Limited / Exclusive pet that came with the Halloween 2021 update. It could have been hatched from the Cursed Egg.
The Huge Pumpkin Cat has a current starting value around 100B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>North Pole Wolf Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/north-pole-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/north-pole-wolf-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>218th most popular pet today
LEGENDARY PET The North Pole Wolf is a Legendary pet that came with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; hatched from the Christmas Tree Egg &amp;amp; Egg of Many Gifts.
The North Pole Wolf has a current starting value around 550M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Orca Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/orca-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/orca-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>57th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Orca is an Exclusive pet from the Axolotl Oceans update as a chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Orca has a current starting value around 4.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Rainbow Unicorn Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/rainbow-unicorn-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/rainbow-unicorn-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>31st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Rainbow Unicorn is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Easter 2022 event &amp;amp; could be hatched from the Exclusive Pets Egg for 800 Robux at a 35% chance.
The Rainbow Unicorn has a current starting value around 5.6B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Storm Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/storm-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/storm-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>186th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Storm Dragon is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Alien update &amp;amp; could have been purchased for 4,999 Robux.
The Storm Dragon has a current starting value around 20B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Update Hype Gift Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/update-hype-gift-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/update-hype-gift-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>101st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Update Hype Gift is an Exclusive gift that you can get by joining a PSX server at least 10 minutes before and update comes out. You can only get this by making sure you are in-game before an update on update day! It contains a variety of exclusive pets.
The Update Hype Gift has a current starting value around 3.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Halloween Gift Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/halloween-gift-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/halloween-gift-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>241st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Halloween Gift is an Exclusive event gift in PSX that was released with the Halloween 2022 update. It cost 1,200 Robux which rewarded you with 10 Halloween Gifts. The pets available to obtain from the gift were (Scary Cat, Scary Corgi, Huge Scary Cat &amp;amp; Huge Scary Corgi.
The Halloween Gift has a current starting value around 12.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Helicopter Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/helicopter-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/helicopter-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>60th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Helicopter Cat is a new Mythical pet in the PSX "Cat World" update! It can be hatched from the Cat Egg or the Yarn Egg.
The Helicopter Cat has a current starting value around 167M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Hippomelon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/hippomelon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/hippomelon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>5th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Hippomelon is an Exclusive pet that was released with April Fools 2022 update. It was obtained by fusing 3 Festive Elves together.
The Hippomelon has a current starting value around 5.2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Keyboard Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/keyboard-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/keyboard-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>29th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Keyboard Cat is an Exclusive pet from the Glitch update as a 50% chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Keyboard Cat has a current starting value around 4.8B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Nature Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/nature-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/nature-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>148th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Nature Dragon is an Exclusive pet from the Glitch update as a 35% chance from the Exclusive Egg.
The Nature Dragon has a current starting value around 6B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Party Crown Duck Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/party-crown-duck-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/party-crown-duck-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>94th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Party Crown Duck is an Exclusive pet that was released with the New Years 2023 update. It could have been hatched from the 2023 Hype Gift at an 80% chance.
The Party Crown Duck has a current starting value around 1.2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Pixel Demon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/pixel-demon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pixel-demon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>48th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Pixel Demon is a Mythical pet that was added with the Pixel World update &amp;amp; can be hatched from the Rainbow Pixel Egg.
The Pixel Demon has a current starting value around 234M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Pog Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/pog-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pog-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>114th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Pog Cat is a Limited edition pet that can no longer be obtained. To get this pet you had to say Knock Knock at the blue door &amp;amp; hatch POG Eggs.
The Pog Cat has a current starting value around 9.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Santa Paws Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/santa-paws-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/santa-paws-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>44th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET Santa Paws is a Mythical pet that came with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; hatched from the Christmas Tree Egg (.000158%) &amp;amp; Egg of Many Gifts (.00863%).
The Santa Paws has a current starting value around 2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>404 Demon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/404-demon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/404-demon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>69th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The 404 Demon is a Mythical pet that can be hatched from the Hacker Egg at around a .0093% chance.
The 404 Demon has a current starting value around 1.1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Doodle Monkey Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/doodle-monkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/doodle-monkey-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>85th most popular pet today
MYTHICAL PET The Doodle Monkey is a mythical pet that was introduced with the Doodle World update. It can be hatched from the Tropical Doodle egg which costs 140k Cartoon coins each.
The Doodle Monkey has a current starting value around 600M gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Doodle Parrot Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/doodle-parrot-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/doodle-parrot-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>79th most popular pet today
SECRET PET The Doodle Parrot is the first-ever "Secret" rarity pet introduced in Pet Simulator X. On release it was the strongest pet in the entire game. For a short period of time you could purchase it from the Mystery Merchant for around 300 million gems. It was quickly removed &amp;amp; now it can only be hatched from the Tropical Doodle Egg.
The Doodle Parrot has a current starting value around 2B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Enchanted Deer Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-enchanted-deer-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-enchanted-deer-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>37th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Enchanted Deer was a limited time huge pet that was introduced on July 21st, 2022 as part of a limited time egg event. It could be hatched from any egg in the game.
The Huge Enchanted Deer has a current starting value around 109.6B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Festive Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-festive-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-festive-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>127th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Festive Cat is an Exclusive pet that came with the Christmas 2021 update &amp;amp; hatched from the Egg of Many Gifts at a 0.00002% chance.
The Huge Festive Cat has a current starting value around 90.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Hacked Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-hacked-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-hacked-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>65th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Hacked Cat is an Exclusive pet that was introduced with the hacker portal update &amp;amp; hatched from the Hacker Egg.
The Huge Hacked Cat has a current starting value around 32B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Pegasus Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-pegasus-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pegasus-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>70th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Pegasus is the most limited &amp;amp; valuable pet to ever come to pet simulator x. It was for sale as an NFT &amp;amp; only 12 people were able to buy them with real money outside of Roblox. Since they are so rare the value is whatever someone is willing to pay.
The Huge Pegasus has a current starting value around 1.5T gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Party Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/party-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/party-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>14th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Party Cat is a Limited pet that was finally released on July 29th, 2022 with the Anniversary Update. It was a 100% chance from the free Anniversary Gift.
The Party Cat has a current starting value around 1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Storm Agony Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/storm-agony-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/storm-agony-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>20th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Storm Agony is an Exclusive pet that was added with the Pixel World update &amp;amp; can be hatched from the Exclusive Pets Egg at a 13% chance.
The Storm Agony has a current starting value around 10B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Crystal Deer Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/crystal-deer-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/crystal-deer-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>78th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Crystal Deer is an Exclusive pet that could be obtained from the Season 1 Gifts DLC in pet sim x.
The Crystal Deer has a current starting value around 9B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Crystal Dog Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/crystal-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/crystal-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>102nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Crystal Dog is an Exclusive pet that could be obtained from the Season 1 Gifts DLC in pet sim x.
The Crystal Dog has a current starting value around 7B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Cupcake Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-cupcake-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-cupcake-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>39th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Cupcake was added in the Mastery Update &amp;amp; can only be obtained as a lucky reward from playtime gifts.
The Huge Cupcake has a current starting value around 20B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Dog Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-dog-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>122nd most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Dog is an Exclusive pet that can only be obtained via code from buying an official Huge Dog plushie or from trading other players.
The Huge Dog has a current starting value around 550B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Dragon Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-dragon-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>88th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Dragon is an Exclusive pet that can only be obtained via code from buying an official Huge Dragon plushie or from trading other players.
The Huge Dragon has a current starting value around 130B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Easter Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-easter-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-easter-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>119th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Easter Cat is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Easter 2022 event &amp;amp; could be hatched from the Legendary orange eggs that spawned every 30 minutes at a 1/20,000 chance.
The Huge Easter Cat has a current starting value around 500B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Hell Rock Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-hell-rock-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-hell-rock-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>1st most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Hell Rock was a limited time huge pet that was introduced on July 21st, 2022 as part of a limited time egg event. It could be hatched from any egg in the game.
The Huge Hell Rock has a current starting value around 10.7B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Techno Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-techno-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-techno-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>116th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Techno Cat is an Exclusive pet that could be obtained from the Season 1 Gifts DLC in pet sim x.
The Huge Techno Cat has a current starting value around 242.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Lightning Bat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/lightning-bat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/lightning-bat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>258th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Lightning Bat is an Exclusive pet that was obtainable from the Exclusive Elemental Egg as a 35% chance.
The Lightning Bat has a current starting value around 13.1B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>How Well Do You Know Roblox Pet Simulator X? (2022 Quiz)</title><link>/post/how-well-do-you-know-roblox-pet-simulator-x-2022-quiz/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-well-do-you-know-roblox-pet-simulator-x-2022-quiz/</guid><description>Last Updated on January 1, 2022 Do you enjoy playing Pet Simulator X? And you would like to test your knowledge on Roblox Pet Sim X to see how much answers you get them right?
Then you are in the right place, let’s find out how good you are!
You can also check out the PSX Value List
Comment down below your score out of /12! and suggest more questions that we can add to this Pet Simulator X Quiz.</description></item><item><title>Huge Cat Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-cat-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>13th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Cat is an Exclusive pet that can only be obtained via code from buying an official Huge Cat plushie or from trading other players.
The Huge Cat has a current starting value around 351B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>Huge Squirrel Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/huge-squirrel-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-squirrel-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>0th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Huge Squirrel is an Exclusive Huge pet which was added with the Doodle World update. It has not yet been announced how to obtain the Huge Squirrel but it will most likely be a merch code.
The Huge Squirrel has a current starting value around 725B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>List of Pets - Pet Simulator X Pet Database</title><link>/post/list-of-pets-pet-simulator-x-pet-database/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/list-of-pets-pet-simulator-x-pet-database/</guid><description>List of Pets - Pet Simulator X Pet Database - PetSimXValues.comPetSimXValues.com TRADERS ONLINE
8,000
DISCORD MEMBERS
130,000
PSX GIVEAWAY AT
130,000</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Heaven Update Log Patch Notes</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-heaven-update-log-patch-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-heaven-update-log-patch-notes/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X continues to remain as one of the more popular games on the platform, and the game has continued to receive additional updates that adds more gameplay. This next update, likely to be called the Heaven update, is going to be bringing the new Pet Collection mechanic that allows for players to collect pets which will earn them additional slots to equip pets! There will also likely be the addition of Heaven island that should bring the final batch of pets and chests to Fantasy World.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Value List in Gems (March 2023)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-in-gems-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-in-gems-march-2023/</guid><description>Last Updated on February 25, 2023 Enjoy playing Pet Simulator X but you are looking to step up your trading game, so you can collect more pets that you have never had, flip pets to gain more gems and get your dream pet.&amp;nbsp;Check out our list of the estimated value&amp;nbsp;list to get an idea of how to win or lose the trade.
Pet Sim X Trading Values Website The trading system in Pet Simulator X makes it more exciting as it allows you to pay gems for pets and exchange pets.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Pet Simulator X All Codes (March 2023)</title><link>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-all-codes-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-all-codes-march-2023/</guid><description>Last Updated on December 4, 2021 New to Roblox Pet Simulator X and you are searching for all the new codes that give free thousands of diamonds and also boost of triple coins and luck.
In this post, we will be covering how you can redeem all the latest codes in Roblox Pet Simulator X and we will keep the code list updated as soon as there are new codes released.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Pet Simulator X has been announced!</title><link>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-has-been-announced/</guid><description>One of the earliest and most well-known simulator games is Pet Simulator. The game remains popular to this day, and has players picking up coins, collecting eggs, and trading pets with other players. A sequel to the game was released, but didn’t seem to spark the same love and attention as the first one. Well, it looks like Big Games Simulators is ready to try again, because Pet Simulator X has now been announced!</description></item><item><title>Super Corgi Value - Pet Sim X Value List</title><link>/post/super-corgi-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/super-corgi-value-pet-sim-x-value-list/</guid><description>137th most popular pet today
EXCLUSIVE PET The Super Corgi is an Exclusive pet that was released with the Easter 2022 event &amp;amp; could be hatched from the Exclusive Pets Egg for 800 Robux at a 50% chance.
The Super Corgi has a current starting value around 4.5B gems when sold at the trading booth.</description></item><item><title>All Star Tower Defense Codes – ASTD [UPDATE] (March 2023)</title><link>/post/all-star-tower-defense-codes-astd-update-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/all-star-tower-defense-codes-astd-update-march-2023/</guid><description>All Star Tower Defense has you collecting well-known anime units and pitting them against waves of enemies that are seeking to destroy your base! If you want to get the best units in the game, then you’re going to need to make sure to redeem codes in ASTD to get gems!
Tower defense games are quite popular within Roblox and outside of it. There’s many different types, so many people are familiar with this format.</description></item><item><title>Clout Cat Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/clout-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/clout-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>How to get Loot Bags in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-loot-bags-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-loot-bags-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has released the new Bank update, and with it has come the new addition of Loot Bags to the game. These are filled with great rewards that will be worthwhile to collect for you players who don’t just afk grind on big chests all day! If you want to know how you can get these and what is inside of them, you can find that information in the guide below!</description></item><item><title>How to get Shiny Pets in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-shiny-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-shiny-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! Now that a new update has been released, you no doubt likely have some questions on how to get access to some of it. Well, if you’re wondering how to get Shiny Pets in Pet Simulator X, we’ll tell you exactly what you need to do!</description></item><item><title>How to get the Huge Peacock in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-peacock-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-peacock-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! With new additions to the game, comes many questions on how things work. If you want to know how to get the Huge Peacock Pet in the game, we’ll tell you how to do it in this guide.
Where to find the Huge Peacock Pet To get the Huge Peacock pet, you will just need to open up the free gifts you get for playing the game.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Huge Snowman in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-snowman-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-snowman-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! Now that the new Christmas update has been released, you no doubt likely have some questions on how to get access to some of it. Well, if you’re wondering how to get the Huge Snowman in Pet Simulator X, we’ll tell you exactly what you need to do!</description></item><item><title>How to get to the Secret Valentine’s Area in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-to-the-secret-valentine-s-area-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-to-the-secret-valentine-s-area-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! With new additions to the game, comes many questions on how things work. If you want to know how to get to the Secret Valentine’s Area in the game, we’ll tell you how to do it in this guide.
Have some pets that you might want to sell or trade?</description></item><item><title>How to use the Bank in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-use-the-bank-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-use-the-bank-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has released the new&amp;nbsp;Bank update, and with it comes the ability to store pets and diamonds away for safekeeping. You will also be able to share your bank with other players, but be aware that you should only do this with people you trust. The bank will have a variety of functions, so let’s clear those up in this guide.
Get free in-game rewards by checking out our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page!</description></item><item><title>What do Diamonds do in Pet Simulator X?</title><link>/post/what-do-diamonds-do-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/what-do-diamonds-do-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>If you are just starting out in the new Pet Simulator X, you might have a fair amount of questions on how the game works. Well, overall it’s a pretty standard simulator game that will have you collecting coins and diamonds to purchase pets. You can also use coins to open up new areas of the map, which you will allow you to earn more currency and upgrade your pets. However, diamonds are a bit more confusing, because their use in the early part of the game isn’t clear.</description></item><item><title>Big Secret Gold Chest in Doodle World in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/big-secret-gold-chest-in-doodle-world-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/big-secret-gold-chest-in-doodle-world-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! With new additions to the game, comes many questions on how things work. If you want to know how to find the Secret Gold Chest in the game, we’ll tell you how to do it in this guide.
Where to find the Secret Gold Chest If you are looking for the Big Secret Gold Chest in Doodle World, you will just need to head to Doodle World and then go to the Doodle Farm area.</description></item><item><title>How to get 25% Mastery in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-25-mastery-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-25-mastery-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! You can now enter into Hardcore Mode, which will allow you to try your luck in a more difficult part of the game. You need to get 25% Mastery to reach the area, and we’ll tell you how to get it.</description></item><item><title>How to get and check Mastery in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-and-check-mastery-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-and-check-mastery-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has added the new Mastery system to the game! This allows you to earn experience by performing basic tasks and gaining XP each time you do. Once you reach certain milestones in a mastery, you will gain a permanent bonus for your character. We’ll walk you through what you need to know about this system in our guide.
You can find all of the working freebies on our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page!</description></item><item><title>How to get Dress Up Achievement in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-dress-up-achievement-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-dress-up-achievement-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>The big new Space Update has been released into Roblox Pet Simulator X, and with it comes another mystery achievement that will have players scratching their heads as to how to get it. First was the PogChamp achievement, which was initially impossible to get and then ended up being pretty easy to complete. Now is the Dress Up achievement, which includes the “Dress to impress” text with it. We’re going to delve into what is known about it in this post.</description></item><item><title>How to get Secret Pets in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-secret-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-secret-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! With new additions to the game, comes many questions on how things work. If you want to know how to get Secret Pets in the game, we’ll tell you how to do it in this guide.
Where to find Secret Pets To get Secret Pets, you will just need to be very lucky when hatching eggs in an area that has these pets available.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Doodle Hoverboard in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-doodle-hoverboard-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-doodle-hoverboard-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! With new additions to the game, comes many questions on how things work. If you want to know how to get the Doodle Hoverboard in the game, we’ll tell you how to do it in this guide.
Where to find the Doodle Hoverboard To get the Doodle Hoverboard, you are going to need to be in Hardcore Mode at the very least.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Cat Plushies Release Date</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-cat-plushies-release-date/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-cat-plushies-release-date/</guid><description>If you’re a fan of Roblox Pet Simulator X then you will be happy to know that you can get some real life swag from the game. The cat that graces the icon of the game on Roblox has been turned into a stuffed plush. This can be purchased soon by visiting the Big Games website. So, if you want something to cuddle at night while you are AFK grinding for coins, then you will want to nab one of these!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Halloween Update Log &amp;amp; Countdown</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-halloween-update-log-countdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-halloween-update-log-countdown/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the largest games on the platform, and on October 23rd, 2021 it will be receiving the big Halloween update for the year! There will be a variety of new eggs to hatch, pets to collect, and a spooky area to explore. If you want to know all about this update, we’ve got all of the known details about it in this post!
The November 2nd, 2021 update details can be found right here: Pet Simulator X Hallowvember Update Log!</description></item><item><title>Shindo Life Mask Codes (March 2023) – New IDs!</title><link>/post/shindo-life-mask-codes-march-2023-new-ids/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/shindo-life-mask-codes-march-2023-new-ids/</guid><description>Roblox Shindo Life has a wide variety of features available to it, and one of those is the ability to customize the mask you wear in the game. If you want to customize this yourself, you can do it by picking out a specific mask design from the Roblox Catalogue. This can be a difficult task to find a mask to your liking. Don’t worry though, because we’ll walk you through the process of finding a great looking new design for your character’s mask in Shindo Life!</description></item><item><title>How to find &amp;amp; unlock the Trading Plaza in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-find-unlock-the-trading-plaza-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-find-unlock-the-trading-plaza-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>The new Trading Plaza in Pet Simulator X is the big new release to the game that was added on October 16th, 2021. Some players are having a bit of trouble finding this place, and understanding what it is all about! We’ll show you where to find it, how to unlock it, and what’s up with the voice chat going on in the area!
Get free in-game rewards by checking out our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page!</description></item><item><title>How to get Dark Matter Pets in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-dark-matter-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-dark-matter-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>In Roblox Pet Simulator X you are looking to collect a variety of different pets, and every now and again an update is released that brings in pets that can evolve to reach a much higher level of power. That’s the case with Dark Matter pets in the game, which can be contained by transforming your pets into pink glowing powerhouses! We’ll walk you through the process of changing your pets to Dark Matter in this guide.</description></item><item><title>How to unlock Hardcore Mode in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-unlock-hardcore-mode-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-unlock-hardcore-mode-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! You can now enter into Hardcore Mode, which will allow you to try your luck in a more difficult part of the game. If you want to know how to unlock it, we’ll tell you how in this guide.
Hardcore Mode Guide To unlock Hardcore Mode in Pet Simulator X, you will first need to be through into The Void.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Advent Calendar Rewards</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-advent-calendar-rewards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-advent-calendar-rewards/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! Now that the new Christmas update has been released, you no doubt likely have some questions on how to get access to some of it. Well, if you’re wondering what all the rewards are in the Pet Simulator X Advent Calendar, we’ll tell you exactly what you want to know!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Axolotl Update Patch Notes</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-axolotl-update-patch-notes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-axolotl-update-patch-notes/</guid><description>The Roblox Pet Simulator X Axolotl update is being released on February 12th, 2022. This release will be bringing some fish based pets that will have you delving underwater to collect your currencies. It is possible that this will be a separate area from Tech World, which has been mostly where players have been spending their time recently. We will see if there’s new currencies to collect as we head into the update.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Space Update – Tech World, Dark Matter Pets</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-space-update-tech-world-dark-matter-pets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-space-update-tech-world-dark-matter-pets/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X which is developed by BIG Games is coming out with another new update that looks to bring a new island to the game, and the ability to transform your pets into Dark Matter! This is a pretty huge addition, and will have players needing to likely make a lot of coins and diamonds to upgrade their pets. We’ll take a look at everything that is currently known about the patch in this post.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X toy pre-order is now available at Target.com</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-toy-pre-order-is-now-available-at-target-com/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-toy-pre-order-is-now-available-at-target-com/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X previously announced a new set of toys would be available with codes that you can pre-order at Target! These have now been released and will likely only be available for a short time before they are sold out.
As of May 20th, 2022 at 7:45am PT the Pet Simulator X toys are now available for&amp;nbsp;pre-order on Target.com!
Each toy is said to come with a redeemable code that you will be able to use in PSX and other Pet Simulator games.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Trading Plaza Update Log</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-trading-plaza-update-log/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-trading-plaza-update-log/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X’s next update will be bringing the Trading Plaza to the game! This will bring a big new area for you to hangout with friends, trade with other players, and just get involved with the community of people who play the game. There’s likely also going to be some new eggs to open and pets to collect!
Get free in-game rewards by checking out our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page!</description></item><item><title>Roblox Pet Simulator X goes private temporarily</title><link>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-goes-private-temporarily/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-goes-private-temporarily/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the most popular games on the platform, so when it went private on March 31st, 2022 a lot of people noticed. Well, it looks like there’s some kind of exploit that has caused problems with the game, so it has been temporarily closed according to the official Twitter account.
Update: Game is available once again, hopefully all of the issues have been fixed!</description></item><item><title>Diamond Cat Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/diamond-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/diamond-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>How to find the Secret Door &amp;amp; Eggs in Pet Simulator X (The Backroom)</title><link>/post/how-to-find-the-secret-door-eggs-in-pet-simulator-x-the-backroom/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-find-the-secret-door-eggs-in-pet-simulator-x-the-backroom/</guid><description>A new achievement has been added to Roblox Pet Simulator X in the Glitch Update, which is The Backroom achievement. This is a special little hidden area you can find that you can unlock and purchase yourself some additional eggs in the game. If you are wondering how to find this new area, we’ll show you exactly what you need to do!
A NEW SECRET DOOR EXISTS: How to unlock the Purple House Door.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Cat Hoverboard in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-cat-hoverboard-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-cat-hoverboard-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X usually has some mysterious tasks to complete, and one of them is obtaining the Cat Hoverboard. Hoverboards will allow you to get around in the game faster when you are just traveling around the map. Rather than just running on foot, you can strap on the board and zoom around. The hoverboards have different speeds based on the difficulty of how you get them. If you’re trying to get the Cat Hoverboard, we’ll explore how it can be done in this guide.</description></item><item><title>How to unlock The Void in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-unlock-the-void-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-unlock-the-void-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X has released the Axolotl update, and with it comes a new area to unlock known as The Void. This is a brand new area you will need to unlock before you can head into the newly added Ocean World in the game. We’ll walk you through the process of what you need to do to unlock this area in the game!
Unlocking The Void To unlock The Void in Pet Simulator X, you will need to head to the Hacker Portal in Tech World.</description></item><item><title>Huge Diamond Cat Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/huge-diamond-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-diamond-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Easter Update – Countdown, Patch Notes, &amp;amp; Leaks!</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-easter-update-countdown-patch-notes-leaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-easter-update-countdown-patch-notes-leaks/</guid><description>While it hasn’t been made super public there will indeed be an Easter update in 2022 for Roblox Pet Simulator X. There has been quite a few leaks for it, which include plenty of pets that will be Easter themed, along with some new huge pets being added to the game. It’s possible there will be a new currency, but the detailed behind the update hasn’t been fully revealed yet!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Rainbow Lucky Block</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-rainbow-lucky-block/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-rainbow-lucky-block/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! With new additions to the game, comes many questions on how things work. If you want to learn more about the Rainbow Lucky Block, we’ll walk you through how you can get them and what they do in this guide.
Rainbow Lucky Block The Rainbow Lucky Block in Pet Simulator X is a rare spawn of the standard Lucky Block.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Game Codes List (March 2023)</title><link>/post/roblox-game-codes-list-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-game-codes-list-march-2023/</guid><description>Roblox has a variety of games and experiences that you can play. The majority of these games feature codes that can be used that will give you freebies that can give you an edge and boost ahead! Not every game has codes, but if they do, you will most likely find them on this list. Each page will be updated as soon as a new code is available, so make sure to bookmark this page and any of the game pages that you play!</description></item><item><title>Titanic Hubert Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/titanic-hubert-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/titanic-hubert-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>How to complete the April Fools tasks in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-complete-the-april-fools-tasks-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-complete-the-april-fools-tasks-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has released a set of April Fools achievements that you can complete to obtain some free currency and an exclusive pet. There’s just three tasks in total, and they are a bit hard to figure out how to complete. If you’re wondering what you need to do to finish these achievements, we’ll tell you how in this guide!
April Fools Tasks Guide There are three challenges you need to complete to earn the free Exclusive Pet for the April Fools Challenge in Pet Simulator X!</description></item><item><title>How to get extra pet slots in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-extra-pet-slots-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-extra-pet-slots-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>If you’re looking to become the king of the leaderboards in Roblox Pet Simulator X then you’re going to need to upgrade your pet slots! There are various ways to do this, but unfortunately the main way is by spending Robux. However, in the Heaven update, you can now boost your pet equip numbers by collecting pets in the game! We will walk you through how it works in this guide.</description></item><item><title>How to get PogChamp achievement in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-pogchamp-achievement-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-pogchamp-achievement-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>If you’re a big time achievement hunter in games, then you’ve no doubt noticed the PogChamp achievement that was added in the first update of Roblox Pet Simulator X. This achievement is interesting because the description reads, “You will never get this achievement.” That has intrigued a lot of players, so we’re going to explore what is known about it in this post.
If you’re in need of some freebies, be sure to check out our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X codes&amp;nbsp;page!</description></item><item><title>How to get the Huge Pumpkin Cat in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-pumpkin-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-pumpkin-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has released the follow-up to its big Halloween update, and now you will be able to possibly add a Huge Pumpkin Cat to your pet collection! If you weren’t able to grab the Huge Cat pet by purchasing the plush, then you will hopefully be able to nab one of these big pets to use instead!
Get free in-game rewards by checking out our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page!</description></item><item><title>How to get the Titanic Cat in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-titanic-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-titanic-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! Now that the new Christmas update has been released, you no doubt likely have some questions on how to get access to some of it. Well, if you’re wondering how to get the Titanic Cat in Pet Simulator X, we’ll tell you exactly what you need to do!</description></item><item><title>Huge Party Axolotl Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/huge-party-axolotl-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-party-axolotl-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>Race Clicker Codes (March 2023)</title><link>/post/race-clicker-codes-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/race-clicker-codes-march-2023/</guid><description>Roblox Race Clicker is an experience developed by 48h Gamers for the platform. In this game, you will be clicking a bunch to gain speed before you race. Once the timer is up you will be running as fast as possible to gain wins by hitting certain milestones. You can then use wins to purchase pets that will help increase your speed and help you win more races!
If you’re looking for freebies then you can find them with our Race Clicker codes list.</description></item><item><title>Where are all the Presents in Pet Simulator X – 20 Locations!</title><link>/post/where-are-all-the-presents-in-pet-simulator-x-20-locations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/where-are-all-the-presents-in-pet-simulator-x-20-locations/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! Now that the new Christmas update has been released, you no doubt likely have some questions on how to get access to some of it. Well, if you’re wondering how to find all of the presents in Pet Simulator X, we’ll tell you exactly what you need to do!</description></item><item><title>Where to find the Elf on the Shelf in Pet Simulator X (Day 22)</title><link>/post/where-to-find-the-elf-on-the-shelf-in-pet-simulator-x-day-22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/where-to-find-the-elf-on-the-shelf-in-pet-simulator-x-day-22/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! Now that the new Christmas update has been released, you no doubt likely have some questions on how to get access to some of it. Well, if you’re wondering how to find the Elf on the Shelf each day in Pet Simulator X, we’ll tell you exactly what you need to do!</description></item><item><title>Anime Fruit Simulator Codes Wiki [Dungeons!] (March 2023)</title><link>/post/anime-fruit-simulator-codes-wiki-dungeons-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/anime-fruit-simulator-codes-wiki-dungeons-march-2023/</guid><description>Roblox Anime Fruit Simulator is an experience developed by Obtain for the platform. In this game, you will be looking to obtain coins by fighting enemies in different worlds. Use that cash to get spins for new fruit and to purchase pets that will help you on your journey. Look to fuse items, obtain boss drops, and unlock all of the worlds to become the number one player in the world.</description></item><item><title>How to do Christmas Event Quests 2022 in Pet Simulator X – Rudolph Hoverboard!</title><link>/post/how-to-do-christmas-event-quests-2022-in-pet-simulator-x-rudolph-hoverboard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-do-christmas-event-quests-2022-in-pet-simulator-x-rudolph-hoverboard/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! Now that the new Christmas update has been released, you no doubt likely have some questions on how to get access to some of it. Well, if you’re wondering how to complete the new Christmas Event Quests for 2022, we’ll tell you exactly what you need to do!</description></item><item><title>How to find the Halloween zone in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-find-the-halloween-zone-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-find-the-halloween-zone-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has releases its big Halloween update, and if you are looking to get to the Halloween zone and purchase up some new pets then we’ll show you where you need to go to get there! However, getting there really isn’t an issue or needed at the moment, because you can only purchase pets at the location. You will need to gather up quite a bit of Candy before you need to head to this area!</description></item><item><title>How to get Pog Cat in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-pog-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-pog-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>The infamous Pog Cat has finally been added to the game for players to obtain in Roblox Pet Simulator X. This thing has been a mystery for a while, ever since the addition of the PogChamp achievement that could not be gotten by players. People were trying to figure out how, but the cat is finally out of the bag and you can get the achievement and the Pog Cat pretty easily!</description></item><item><title>Love Lion Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/love-lion-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/love-lion-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Bank Update Log Patch Notes</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-bank-update-log-patch-notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-bank-update-log-patch-notes/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is receiving the new Bank Update on December 4th, 2021! This release brings the new bank that you can visit, which allows you to store pets, share cross-server with friends, and earn interest on your diamonds. There are also now loot bags, which will pop out of coins, chests, and other breakables. These contain large quantities of rewards including boosts!
There will hopefully be a new code added in this update, which you will find on our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Fusing Guide – Christmas Update!</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-fusing-guide-christmas-update/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-fusing-guide-christmas-update/</guid><description>In Roblox Pet Simulator X, one of the best ways to get some powerful pets is to fuse some of your older pets together. While you will have to say goodbye to those pets that have served you well in the past, you will get some new pets that will help you head into the future! If you want to know how best to fuse pets in Pet Simulator X, then we’ll show you how in this guide.</description></item><item><title>Roblox Pet Simulator X toys coming soon</title><link>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-toys-coming-soon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/roblox-pet-simulator-x-toys-coming-soon/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has been a bit quiet lately, as updates haven’t been added to the game as frequently as they have in the past. However, they have just announced something new is coming, unfortunately it’s not going to be totally in-game related!
Update: Pet Simulator X toys are now available for pre-order on Target.com!
BIG Games, the developers of Pet Simulator X, have announced that they are releasing a collectible toy line for the game.</description></item><item><title>What is a merch code in Pet Simulator X?</title><link>/post/what-is-a-merch-code-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/what-is-a-merch-code-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>There seems to be a fair amount of confusion surrounding the “merch code” in Roblox Pet Simulator X. People are wondering how to get it, what it does, and if it is free. Well, you’ll likely be a bit disappointed with the actual answer, because these are going to be extremely limited, and they certainly aren’t going to be free! We’ll walk you through what you need to know in this post.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Huge Hacker Cat in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-hacker-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-hacker-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>A bunch of new pets were added to Roblox Pet Simulator X in the&amp;nbsp;Glitch Update! One of these is the new Huge Hacker Cat, which is another of these oversized pets that can be collected. The huge pets are pretty hard to get, and you will have to be incredibly lucky or trade with another player to ever actually get one. If you’re wondering what you could do to get the Huge Hacker Cat, we’ll show you in this guide.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Huge Hell Rock in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-hell-rock-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-hell-rock-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! While there hasn’t been a patch in a while, a minor update has added a new huge pet to the game that can be obtained by anyone very simply! We’ll teach you how to get it in this guide.
Huge Hell Rock Guide To get the Huge Hell Rock in Pet Simulator X, you just need to open up any egg in the game to have a chance to hatch one.</description></item><item><title>How to get to Tech World in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-to-tech-world-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-to-tech-world-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X just got the brand new Space Update, which has unlocked the new stage known as Tech World. This is just like Fantasy World, but will require you to pay a hefty sum of coins to enter into the new area. We’ll tell you exactly all you need to know to enter into this futuristic place.
Get free in-game rewards by checking out our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page! Also, check out the patch notes for the new&amp;nbsp;Space Update.</description></item><item><title>How to make Huge Pets in Pet Simulator X – Huge-a-Tron Machine!</title><link>/post/how-to-make-huge-pets-in-pet-simulator-x-huge-a-tron-machine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-make-huge-pets-in-pet-simulator-x-huge-a-tron-machine/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the biggest games on the platform, so when they release a new update people are clamoring to try out the new content! With new additions to the game, comes many questions on how things work. If you want to know how to make Huge Pets in the game, we’ll tell you how to do it in this guide.
How to craft Huge Pets To make Huge Pets, you will need to access the Huge-a-Tron machine.</description></item><item><title>Mystery Merchant Spawn Times &amp;amp; Location in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/mystery-merchant-spawn-times-location-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/mystery-merchant-spawn-times-location-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has released the follow-up to its big Halloween update, and with that update is the release of the Mystery merchant which will temporarily appear on all servers. If you want to get access to this merchant, who sell pets at a big discount, we will show you how!
Get free in-game rewards by checking out our&amp;nbsp;Pet Simulator X Codes&amp;nbsp;page!
Mystery Merchant Guide To find the Mystery Merchant, you will need to head either to the Cave area in Spawn World or you will need to go to the Trading Plaza.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Dragon and Dog Plush Countdown – Release Date &amp;amp; Time!</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-dragon-and-dog-plush-countdown-release-date-time/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-dragon-and-dog-plush-countdown-release-date-time/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is one of the most popular and well-known games on the platform. It has influenced many of the games that have been releasing lately, and continues to look to innovate in the space. One of the things that Big Games has been doing is creating merchandise for the game. In particular, the Cat Plush was released in 2021 and sold out exceptionally fast. If you missed out on that one, you can now hope to get the Dragon and Dog stuffed animals that will be available very soon.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Ranks List (March 2023)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-ranks-list-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-ranks-list-march-2023/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X can be a pretty grindy game, and if you want the best pets, then you’re going to need a fair amount of lucky boosts. If you don’t want to shell out Robux, then hitting the Rank Rewards chest when it isn’t on cooldown is one of the best ways to do this. The higher your rank in the game, the more rewards you will get for visiting it.</description></item><item><title>Pop Cat Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/pop-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pop-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>Update Hype Gift Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/update-hype-gift-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/update-hype-gift-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>How to find Easter Eggs in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-find-easter-eggs-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-find-easter-eggs-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X has released its Easter update for 2022 on April 17th. In it you will be able to find yourself a variety of different themed pets on the holiday. While normally there would be a new currency to acquire, instead you will be hunting down eggs that have pets inside of them! If you want to know how to find these Easter eggs in the game, we’ll tell you how in this guide!</description></item><item><title>How to make rainbow pets In Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-make-rainbow-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-make-rainbow-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Bored of normal pets? Need something with a little more kick than the Golden pets? Then look no further than our guide on how to make Rainbow Pets in Pet Simulator X to really get your team looking fresh.
The Roblox game Pet Simulator X is known for its delightful collection of creatures, and the different levels of power they can provide. The bright and shiny Rainbow animals provide better abilities and higher stats than the glistening Gold ones, but this does come with a cost.</description></item><item><title>Huge Pop Cat Value &amp;amp; Price (March 2023) – Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/huge-pop-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pop-cat-value-price-march-2023-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game for Roblox. In this game, players embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. One of the best parts is that you get to hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities. The goal of the game is to become the ultimate pet collector by obtaining the rarest and strongest pets!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Codes (March 2023)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-codes-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-codes-march-2023/</guid><description>Roblox Pet Simulator X is the newest follow up to the popular Pet Simulator series! This game will have you collecting coins and diamonds to purchase eggs, which you can then hatch to obtain legendary pets like dragons or unicorns! there will be areas to explore, eggs to find, secret to uncover, and you will be able to trade pets with other players! If you have some duplicate pets, you can fuse them together or use them to get new ones!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Enchantments List</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-enchantments-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-enchantments-list/</guid><description>If you’ve been looking to get the maximum benefit out of your pets in Roblox Pet Simulator X then you are going to want to make sure they have enchantments on them. These used to be only available at random when you bought a pet, but you can now gamble your way to them by using the Enchantment Circle. We’ll be taking a look at all of the enchantments you can get in the game in this post!</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Scary Cat</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-scary-cat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-scary-cat/</guid><description>Looking to pick up the Pet Simulator X Scary Cat in Roblox? In Pet Simulator X, one of the big things is getting new pets and taking care of them. Getting event exclusive pets are also really great as they can have quite a bit of value
The Halloween event brings in two new pets, Scary cat and Scary Corgi. With these two new pets comes new eggs, and other things to do in game.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Value List [Hologram] (March 2023) – Diamond Prices!</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-hologram-march-2023-diamond-prices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-hologram-march-2023-diamond-prices/</guid><description>Pet Simulator X aka PSX is a popular collection game on the online gaming platform Roblox. In this game, players take on the role of a pet and embark on an adventure to collect coins, gems, and other valuable items. It offers a vast and colorful open world where players can explore different zones and interact with other players. Players can hatch eggs to collect new pets, each with its own unique abilities.</description></item><item><title>Plushie Simulator Codes (March 2023) – Gifts Update!</title><link>/post/plushie-simulator-codes-march-2023-gifts-update/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/plushie-simulator-codes-march-2023-gifts-update/</guid><description>In Roblox Plushie Simulator, you will be getting your very own plush toy that you can use to earn more plushies. Upgrade your toy and energy supply so that you can purchase pets and climb in ranks so that you can gain even more plushies. Once you’ve upgraded your character, you can head to new worlds to explore and purchase more powerful pets. Seek to become the best plushie owner in the game!</description></item><item><title>How to get the Titanic Jolly Cat in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-titanic-jolly-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-titanic-jolly-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>In what is probably one last Christmas hurrah for Pet Simulator X, a whole new kind of pet has made it into the game. If you're wondering how to get the Titanic Jolly Cat added to your Roblox collection, keep reading. It's not as hard as you'd expect.
The all-new Titanic Jolly Cat is the biggest pet in the game. And it very well could be the biggest we'll ever see.</description></item><item><title>How To Make Dark Matter Pets In Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-make-dark-matter-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-make-dark-matter-pets-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Wondering how to make Dark Matter pets in Pet Simulator X? Had enough of watching others blow apart boxes with their small army of Dark Matter buddies in this mega-popular Roblox game? Making Dark Matter pets in Pet Simulator X is a lot easier than the high-level players would have you think. The rewards are greater with better pets for sure, but the general idea remains the same.
For now, the Dark Matter pets added with Update 11 are the strongest type of pets in the game.</description></item><item><title>How to unlock the Cat Throne Room in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-unlock-the-cat-throne-room-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-unlock-the-cat-throne-room-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Wondering how to unlock the Cat Throne Room in Pet Simulator X? You're not the only one. Not long after a secret door was added for the Hardcore update, another was added, hiding the Cat Throne Room behind it.
The new Pet Simulator X update has landed, bringing the exclusive Hardcore mode to the game. Though it's the focus of the update, a bunch of little secret doors have appeared throughout the old worlds as well, creating confusion among the players who struggle to find them or just can't open them.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Christmas 2022</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-christmas-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-christmas-2022/</guid><description>Despite moving to a weekly update schedule late this year, there's still a massive Pet Simulator X Christmas update coming to Roblox. There's no saying it's a dedicated Christmas event like the hallmark PSX Easter 2022 drop, either, meaning it might be followed up with even more the week after.
Down below, we'll take a look at what we know about the Pet Simulator X Winter update so far, using Preston's tweets and hints to work things out.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Easter Update</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-easter-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-easter-update/</guid><description>In a surprise Sunday twist, an unexpected Pet Simulator X Easter update went live, bringing with it loads of new Easter pets for the already overflowing pet taming clicker game. But the new Pet Simulator X easter update doesn't work like a standard update, causing some confusion. Here's how to get all the Easter pets before they go away when the Pet Simulator X Easter update finally concludes.
Down below, we're going to briefly go over how you can get your hands on the limited-time Easter pets in Pet Simulator X, how to maximise your chances of finding them, and why you'll want to grab as many as you can.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Halloween event</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-halloween-event/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-halloween-event/</guid><description>November 5, 2022: The Halloween Pet Simulator X event is officially over, but the Cat World update is in to take its place. Check out how to get the Huge Balloon Cat.Looking for details about the Pet Simulator X Halloween event in Roblox? Well you're in luck! There's some cool stuff happening with this event, and we have all the details in this guide.
Advertisement
This event runs similarly to last year's event, with various currencies, pets and eggs that are available to pick up.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Mystery Merchant</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-mystery-merchant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-mystery-merchant/</guid><description>Though you spent much of your early time in Pet Simulator X instructing your fuzzy buddies to smash up crates, coin piles, lockers, chests, and safes while you scurry around grabbing their contents, it's far from the only way to afford new pets. The Pet Simulator X Mystery Merchant is one way to avoid the gacha element of this popular Roblox game, and we're going to take the mystery out of their name by divulging everything you need to know about them.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X pets (November 2022)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-pets-november-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-pets-november-2022/</guid><description>November 5, 2022: We've added the Cat World pets from the latest Pet Simulator X update.
As the name suggests, there are plenty of animals in Pet Simulator X to collect. As such, we've got a comprehensive list of all Pet Simulator X pets, as well as the corresponding eggs you can hatch them from. There are plenty out there, so you'll have tons of furry friends to care for in no time.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Traveling Merchant</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-traveling-merchant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-traveling-merchant/</guid><description>One way to quickly make some serious progress in one of the biggest Roblox games around is to watch for the Pet Simulator X Traveling Merchant around like a hawk. The tricky vendor sells some incredibly rare pets, allowing anyone with pockets full of diamonds to dodge gacha eggs and grab some powerful pets without much hassle, and we're going to show you how.
Our Pet Simulator X Traveling Merchant guide will break down what the Traveling Merchant does in Pet Simulator, what time it spawns, where it spawns, and what you can expect to buy from it.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Huge Cupcake in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-huge-cupcake-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-huge-cupcake-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>April 18, 2022: With new pets right around the corner, learn how to get Huge Cupcake in Pet Simulator X before it's just not really worth trying for.
With a fresh update to explore, everyone is wondering how to get Huge Cupcake in Pet Simulator X. Unlocking it is no easy feat, so we're here to help explain exactly what the Huge Cupcake is, and how you can get your hands on the biggest new pet in one of the biggest Roblox games around.</description></item><item><title>How To Get the Huge Easter Cat in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-easter-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-huge-easter-cat-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>After the rush for the Huge Cupcake pet, knowing how to get the Huge Easter Cat in Pet Simulator X is the topic on everyone's minds right now. The limited-time buddy has arrived to take to usurp the throne of the Huge Cupcake as the exclusive pet everybody wants. Introduced via the substantial and surprising Pet Simulator X Easter update, here's how to get the Huge Easter Cat, and a few tips on how to increase your odds.</description></item><item><title>How to get the Pet Simulator X Huge Balloon Cat</title><link>/post/how-to-get-the-pet-simulator-x-huge-balloon-cat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-get-the-pet-simulator-x-huge-balloon-cat/</guid><description>November 9, 2022: The Blue Huge Balloon Cat is available in the shop for the next three days.
ThePet Simulator X Huge Balloon Cat is the latest big pet to arrive in-game. Added through the November 5 update, it's sure to be a rare and sought-after pet just like the Huge Cupcake. Until the next comes along, you'll want to get this for trades and bragging rights. Here's how it's done.</description></item><item><title>How to Trade in Pet Simulator X</title><link>/post/how-to-trade-in-pet-simulator-x/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/how-to-trade-in-pet-simulator-x/</guid><description>Collecting all the Roblox pets is no easy feat, so you'll need to know how to trade in Pet Simulator X. It's one of the most popular games on the entire platform, and one of the best ways to unlock top tier pets is by swapping with other players in the lobby. Luckily, this guide will explain everything you need to know about trading in Pet Simulator X.
We'll give you some instructions on how to trade in Pet Simulator X, which includes how to initiate a trade, and what happens once you're in a trading lobby.</description></item><item><title>HUGE Love Lamb Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/huge-love-lamb-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-love-lamb-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for HUGE Love Lamb Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
HUGE Love Lamb Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] HUGE Love Lamb Normal Value: 700,000,000,000 HUGE Love Lamb Golden Value: 1,200,000,000,000 HUGE Love Lamb Rainbow Value: 3,000,000,000,000 HUGE Love Lamb Dark Matter Value:&amp;nbsp; HUGE Love Lamb Normal Gem Value: 70,000,000,000 HUGE Love Lamb Golden Gem Value: 120,000,000,000 HUGE Love Lamb Rainbow Gem Value: 300,000,000,000 Shiny HUGE Love Lamb Value:&amp;nbsp; Shiny Golden HUGE Love Lamb Value:&amp;nbsp; Shiny Rainbow HUGE Love Lamb Value:&amp;nbsp; Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X value list (March 2023)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-march-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-march-2023/</guid><description>March 11, 2023: We've updated the list with preliminary PSX St. Patricks Day pet prices. They'll fall rapidly throughout the event and spike after, so think before you trade.Looking to trade your pets away from piles of diamonds? We have you covered with this Pet Simulator X value list. We'll help you familiarise yourself with the fluctuating in-game costs of each pet in this ever-popular Roblox trading game to ensure you never get ripped off or scammed.</description></item><item><title>Sword Slasher Codes Wiki Roblox[NEW]</title><link>/post/sword-slasher-codes-wiki-roblox-new/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sword-slasher-codes-wiki-roblox-new/</guid><description>Read on for Sword Slasher Wiki for codes. A complete list of all new Sword Slasher Codes Roblox to redeem in the Roblox.
Sword Slasher Wiki For Codes⇓
Published by E25, Sword Slasher is a Roblox game.
In this post, we will share the Sword Slasher Codes Roblox. Please bookmark this page and visit this page often for the latest list of working codes.
We checked for new Sword Slasher Codes Roblox on February 14th, 2023.</description></item><item><title>Axolotl Hype Gift Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/axolotl-hype-gift-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/axolotl-hype-gift-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Axolotl Hype Gift Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Axolotl Hype Gift Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Axolotl Hype Gift Normal Value: 2,500,000,000 Axolotl Hype Gift Golden Value: Axolotl Hype Gift Rainbow Value: Axolotl Hype Gift Normal Gem Value: 2,500,000,000 Axolotl Hype Gift Golden Gem Value: Axolotl Hype Gift Rainbow Gem Value: Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes
Pet value changes; it may drop or see an increase, we will try our best to provide the most accurate and updated values of the pet.</description></item><item><title>Huge Chameleon Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/huge-chameleon-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-chameleon-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Huge Chameleon Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Huge Chameleon Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Huge Chameleon Normal Value: 600,000,000,000 Huge Chameleon Golden Value: 1,400,000,000,000 Huge Chameleon Rainbow Value: 2,750,000,000,000 Huge Chameleon Normal Gem Value: 60,000,000,000 Huge Chameleon Golden Gem Value: 140,000,000,000 Huge Chameleon Rainbow Gem Value: 275,000,000,000 Shiny Huge Chameleon Value: 1,900,000,000,000 Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes
Pet value changes; it may drop or see an increase, we will try our best to provide the most accurate and updated values of the pet.</description></item><item><title>Huge Diamond Cat Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/huge-diamond-cat-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-diamond-cat-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Huge Diamond Cat Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Huge Diamond Cat Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Huge Diamond Cat Normal Value: 6,750,000,000,000 Huge Diamond Cat Golden Value: 12,250,000,000,000 Huge Diamond Cat Rainbow Value: 35,000,000,000,000 Huge Diamond Cat Normal Gem Value: 325,000,000,000 Huge Diamond Cat Golden Gem Value: 550,000,000,000 Huge Diamond Cat Rainbow Gem Value: 1,700,000,000,000 Shiny Huge Diamond Cat Value: Soon Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes</description></item><item><title>Huge Orca Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/huge-orca-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-orca-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Huge Orca Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Huge Orca Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Huge Orca Normal Value: 460,000,000,000 Huge Orca Golden Value: 1,100,000,000,000 Huge Orca Rainbow Value: 2,000,000,000,000 Huge Orca Normal Gem Value: 46,000,000,000 Huge Orca Golden Gem Value: 105,000,000,000 Huge Orca Rainbow Gem Value: 200,000,000,000 Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes
Pet value changes; it may drop or see an increase, we will try our best to provide the most accurate and updated values of the pet.</description></item><item><title>Huge Pterodactyl Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/huge-pterodactyl-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pterodactyl-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Huge Pterodactyl Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Huge Pterodactyl Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Huge Pterodactyl Normal Value: 225,000,000,000 Huge Pterodactyl Golden Value: 500,000,000,000 Huge Pterodactyl Rainbow Value: 1,500,000,000,000 Huge Pterodactyl Normal Gem Value: 25,000,000,000 Huge Pterodactyl Golden Gem Value: 60,000,000,000 Huge Pterodactyl Rainbow Gem Value: 150,000,000,000 Shiny Huge Pterodactyl Value: 600,000,000,000 Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes
Pet value changes; it may drop or see an increase, we will try our best to provide the most accurate and updated values of the pet.</description></item><item><title>Lovemelon Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/lovemelon-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/lovemelon-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Lovemelon Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Lovemelon Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Lovemelon Normal Value:&amp;nbsp; Lovemelon Golden Value:&amp;nbsp; Lovemelon Rainbow Value: Lovemelon Normal Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Lovemelon Golden Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Lovemelon Rainbow Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes
Pet value changes; it may drop or see an increase, we will try our best to provide the most accurate and updated values of the pet.</description></item><item><title>Strong Muscle Simulator Codes Wiki Roblox[NEW]</title><link>/post/strong-muscle-simulator-codes-wiki-roblox-new/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/strong-muscle-simulator-codes-wiki-roblox-new/</guid><description>Read on for Strong Muscle Simulator Wiki for codes. A complete list of all new Strong Muscle Simulator Codes Roblox to redeem in the Roblox.
Strong Muscle Simulator Wiki For Codes⇓
Published by TPC Simulators, Strong Muscle Simulator is a Roblox game.
In this post, we will share the Strong Muscle Simulator Codes Roblox. Please bookmark this page and visit this page often for the latest list of working codes.</description></item><item><title>Strong Pet Simulator Codes Wiki(NEW)</title><link>/post/strong-pet-simulator-codes-wiki-new/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/strong-pet-simulator-codes-wiki-new/</guid><description>Looking for Strong Pet Simulator Wiki for codes? Read on for Strong Pet Simulator Codes Wiki where we have shared all the new working codes!&amp;nbsp;
Strong Pet Simulator Wiki⇓ Published by Impulsive Heroe’s, Strong Pet Simulator is a Roblox game where players will be delivering items along with their pets to earn energy. Energy can be used to buy new pets, upgrade pets, get tokens, and also unlock tokens. Token in Strong Pet Simulator Roblox is another in-game item that will help you to upgrade the forms of the pets and increase their power.</description></item><item><title>Super Anime Simulator Codes Wiki Roblox [NEW]</title><link>/post/super-anime-simulator-codes-wiki-roblox-new/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/super-anime-simulator-codes-wiki-roblox-new/</guid><description>Read on for Super Anime Simulator Wiki for codes. A complete list of all new Super Anime Simulator Codes Roblox to redeem in the Roblox.
Article Contents:
Super Anime Simulator Wiki For Codes⇓
Published by cdxy Games, Super Anime Simulator is a Roblox game.
In this post, we will share the Super Anime Simulator Codes Roblox. Please bookmark this page and visit this page often for the latest list of working codes.</description></item><item><title>Custom PC Tycoon Codes Wiki(NEW)</title><link>/post/custom-pc-tycoon-codes-wiki-new/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/custom-pc-tycoon-codes-wiki-new/</guid><description>Looking for Custom PC Tycoon Wiki for codes? Read on for Custom PC Tycoon Codes Wiki where we have shared all the new working codes!&amp;nbsp;
Published by Fallen worlds official group, Custom PC Tycoon is a Roblox game where players build the PC of their dreams. They build a PC using customizable parts and sell it for cash. Players can later use the saved cash to buy better parts and build the best and powerful PC.</description></item><item><title>Fruit Battlegrounds Tier List: Fruit Tier List(April 2023)</title><link>/post/fruit-battlegrounds-tier-list-fruit-tier-list-april-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/fruit-battlegrounds-tier-list-fruit-tier-list-april-2023/</guid><description>Read on for Fruit Battlegrounds Tier List ranking the best fruit.&amp;nbsp;
Fruit Battlegrounds Tier List: Fruit Tier List
The following Fruit Battlegrounds tier list ranks fruits in these tiers;&amp;nbsp;
Tier 0: OP Tier 1: Best Tier 2: Good Tier 3: Decent Tier 4: Average Tier 5: Below-Average Tier 6: Worst Also, see – Fruit Battlegrounds Trello, Fruit Battlegrounds Codes
Fruit Battlegrounds Tier List: Tier 0 Timeskip Rubber – Tier 0 Phoenix – Tier 0 Gravity – Zushi Zushi No Mi – Tier 0 Quake – Gura Gura No Mi – Tier 0 Dragon – Tier 0 Dough – Tier 0 All Mythical Grade fruits are excellent.</description></item><item><title>Huge Party Axolotl Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/huge-party-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-party-axolotl-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Huge Party Axolotl Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Huge Party Axolotl Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Huge Party Axolotl Normal Value: 1,100,000,000,000 Huge Party Axolotl Golden Value: 2,200,000,000,000 Huge Party Axolotl Rainbow Value: 7,000,000,000,000 Huge Party Axolotl Normal Gem Value: 110,000,000,000 Huge Party Axolotl Golden Gem Value: 220,000,000,000 Huge Party Axolotl Rainbow Gem Value: 350,000,000,000 Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes</description></item><item><title>Huge Pop Cat Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/huge-pop-cat-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pop-cat-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Huge Pop Cat Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Huge Pop Cat Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Huge Pop Cat Normal Value: 550,000,000,000 Huge Pop Cat Golden Value: 9,000,000,000,000 Huge Pop Cat Rainbow Value: Huge Pop Cat Normal Gem Value: 55,000,000,000 Huge Pop Cat Golden Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Huge Pop Cat Rainbow Gem Value: 450,000,000,000 Shiny Huge Pop Cat Value:&amp;nbsp; Shiny Golden Huge Pop Cat Value:&amp;nbsp; Shiny Rainbow Huge Pop Cat Value Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Codes Wiki | PSX Codes(NEW)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-codes-wiki-psx-codes-new/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-codes-wiki-psx-codes-new/</guid><description>Our Pet Simulator X Codes Wiki 2022 Roblox has the latest list of working PSX codes. Get the latest PSX codes and redeem some good rewards.
Article Contents⇓
Pet Simulator X Codes Wiki Roblox⇓ We provide the fastest updates and full coverage on the new and working Pet Simulator X Codes Wiki 2022 Roblox. Make sure to bookmark this page for new code updates and also check out our Roblox Games’ Codes Library.</description></item><item><title>PSX Value List 2023 | Pet Sim X(Pet Simulator X Value List 2023)[UPDATED]</title><link>/post/psx-value-list-2023-pet-sim-x-pet-simulator-x-value-list-2023-updated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/psx-value-list-2023-pet-sim-x-pet-simulator-x-value-list-2023-updated/</guid><description>PSX Value List – read on for an updated Pet Sim X value list 2023 featuring all the Pet Simulator X pets.&amp;nbsp;
Pet Simulator X Value List 2023 Wiki | PSX Value List The following PSX Value List 2023[Pet Sim X] – Pet Simulator X value list 2023 covers all the pets and their values in all forms; normal, golden, rainbow, and dark matter. Also, if you are new to the game, please check out the working Pet Simulator X codes for freebies.</description></item><item><title>Rose Egg Location In Pet Simulator X[PSX]</title><link>/post/rose-egg-location-in-pet-simulator-x-psx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/rose-egg-location-in-pet-simulator-x-psx/</guid><description>Wondering how to get Ross Egg in Pet Simulator X? Here’s everything you need to know about PSX Ross Egg – the secret area where you can find this egg!
Rose Egg Location In Pet Simulator X[PSX] Ross Egg is located in a secret area. The secret area is behind the waterfall, which is located in Valentine’s Event location. First, from the Spawn area, head to Valentine’s Event area.&amp;nbsp;
Go Upstairs.</description></item><item><title>Titanic Hubert Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/titanic-hubert-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/titanic-hubert-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Titanic Hubert Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Titanic Hubert Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Titanic Hubert Normal Value: 70,000,000,000,000 Titanic Hubert Golden Value:&amp;nbsp; Titanic Hubert Rainbow Value: Titanic Hubert Normal Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Titanic Hubert Golden Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Titanic Hubert Rainbow Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes
Pet value changes; it may drop or see an increase, we will try our best to provide the most accurate and updated values of the pet.</description></item><item><title>Valentines Cat Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED]</title><link>/post/valentines-cat-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/valentines-cat-value-pet-sim-x-updated/</guid><description>Read on for Valentines Cat Value In PSX[Pet Simulator X].
Valentines Cat Value – Pet Sim X [UPDATED] Valentines Cat Normal Value: 8,000,000 Valentines Cat Golden Value: 20,000,000 Valentines Cat Rainbow Value: 60,000,000 Valentines Cat Dark Matter Value: 200,000,000 Valentines Cat Normal Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Valentines Cat Golden Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Valentines Cat Rainbow Gem Value:&amp;nbsp; Also, see – Pet Sim X [PSX] Value List, Pet Simulator X Codes
Pet value changes; it may drop or see an increase, we will try our best to provide the most accurate and updated values of the pet.</description></item><item><title>Huge Crystal Dog Value</title><link>/post/huge-crystal-dog-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-crystal-dog-value/</guid><description>Huge Crystal Dog Value (N) Pet Value:💎310,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎450B
(G) Pet Value:💎2,700,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎Soon
(R) Pet Value:💎4,750,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎Soon
What is Huge Crystal Dog? Huge Crystal Dog is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X from Season 1 DLC Gifts. How much is Huge Crystal Dog worth? The current Huge Crystal Dog value is 310,000,000,000 diamonds for the Rainbow version.
How to get Huge Crystal Dog?</description></item><item><title>Huge Skeleton Value</title><link>/post/huge-skeleton-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-skeleton-value/</guid><description>Huge Skeleton Value (N) Pet Value:💎700,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎70B
(G) Pet Value:💎2,600,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎200B
(R) Pet Value:💎20,000,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎1T
What is Huge Skeleton? Huge Skeleton is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X from Season 1 DLC Gifts. How much is Huge Skeleton worth? The current Huge Skeleton value is 700,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.
How to get Huge Skeleton? Huge Skeleton can be obtained from an Exclusive DLC Gift.</description></item><item><title>Huge Snowman Value</title><link>/post/huge-snowman-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-snowman-value/</guid><description>Huge Snowman Value (N) Pet Value:💎750,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎85B
(G) Pet Value:💎2,250,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎185B
(R) Pet Value:💎14,000,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎Soon
What is Huge Snowman in Pet Simulator X? Huge Snowman is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was released on December 17, 2022.
How much is Huge Snowman worth? The current Huge Snowman value is estimated to be around 750,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.</description></item><item><title>Koala Value</title><link>/post/koala-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/koala-value/</guid><description>Koala Value Normal:💎1,000,000,000
What is Koala? Koala is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Pixel update.
How much is Koala worth? The current Koala value is 1,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Koala? Koala is obtainable for a limited amount of time by buying an Exclusive Pets Egg from the Exclusive Shop. It costs 800 Roblux for a chance to obtain one, and 2400 for three chances.</description></item><item><title>Otter Value</title><link>/post/otter-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/otter-value/</guid><description>Otter Value (N) Pet Value:💎3,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎900M
What is Otter? Otter is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Christmas Event.
How much is Otter worth? The current Otter value is estimated to be around 3,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Otter? Otter was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time. It cost 599 Robux.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Leaks – Leaked Pets</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-leaks-leaked-pets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-leaks-leaked-pets/</guid><description>Here is our Pet Simulator X leaks guide. Leaking all of the new pets coming in the next big update for Pet Sim X!
Pet Simulator X Leaks The next update will very likely feature the new Exclusive Egg 11 (Hologram Egg) and also two new Kawaii areas named Dojo and Tokyo Alley.
New Kawaii World Pets Unknown Huge Pet Huge Gleebo the Alien Value
Exclusive Egg 11 (Hologram Egg) Pets Pet Simulator X Leaks: Unreleased pets These pets have been leaked.</description></item><item><title>Pony Value</title><link>/post/pony-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pony-value/</guid><description>Pony Value Normal:💎2,250,000,000
What is Pony? Pony is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Pixel update.
How much is Pony worth? The current Pony value is 2,250,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Pony? Pony is obtainable for a limited amount of time by buying an Exclusive Pets Egg from the Exclusive Shop. It costs 800 Roblux for a chance to obtain one, and 2400 for three chances.</description></item><item><title>Sock Corgi Value</title><link>/post/sock-corgi-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sock-corgi-value/</guid><description>Sock Corgi Value Pet Value:💎27,000,000,000
Gem Value:💎7.5B
What is Sock Corgi? Sock Corgi is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Alien Update, and is a re-skin of both the Corgi and Zombie Corgi pets.
How much is Sock Corgi worth? The current Sock Corgi value is estimated to be around 27,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Sock Corgi? Sock Corgi was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Turkey Value</title><link>/post/turkey-value/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/turkey-value/</guid><description>Turkey Value Normal:💎350,000
Golden:💎1,720,000
Rainbow:💎6,000,000
Dark Matter:💎27,500,000
HC Normal: 💎N/A
HC Golden: 💎N/A
HC Rainbow: 💎N/A
HC DM:💎N/A
What is Turkey in Pet Simulator X? Turkey is a Mythical pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Autumn Event, which was released on November 19, 2022.
It is currently the second-strongest pet in the game. Overtaken by Lucki.
How much is Turkey worth? The current Turkey value is estimated to be around 350,000 diamonds for the normal version.</description></item><item><title>Festive Elf Value</title><link>/post/festive-elf-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/festive-elf-value/</guid><description>Festive Elf Value Normal:💎50,000,000
Golden:💎50,000,000
Rainbow:💎50,000,000
Dark Matter:💎50,000,000
What is Festive Elf? Festive Elf is a Rare rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Christmas 2021 Update.
How much is Festive Elf worth? The current Festive Elf value is estimated to be around 50,000,000 diamonds.
Hippomelon A limited Exclusive pet called Hippomelon can be obtained by fusing three Festive Elves during April Fools 2022.</description></item><item><title>Grumpy Cat Value</title><link>/post/grumpy-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/grumpy-cat-value/</guid><description>Grumpy Cat Value Pet Value:💎80,000,000,000
Gem Value:💎16B
What is Grumpy Cat? Grumpy Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Tech Update.
How much is Grumpy Cat worth? The current Grumpy Cat value is estimated to be around 80,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Grumpy Cat? Grumpy Cat was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Lava Scorpion Value</title><link>/post/lava-scorpion-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/lava-scorpion-value/</guid><description>Lava Scorpion Value (N) Pet Value:💎30,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎5.5B
What is Lava Scorpion? Lava Scorpion is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Steampunk Update.
How much is Lava Scorpion worth? The current Lava Scorpion value is estimated to be around 30,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Lava Scorpion? Lava Scorpion was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Mrs. Claws Value</title><link>/post/mrs-claws-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/mrs-claws-value/</guid><description>Mrs. Claws Value Normal:💎15,000,000
Golden:💎50,000,000
Rainbow:💎150,000,000
Dark Matter:💎400,000,000
HC Normal: 💎125,000,000
HC Golden: 💎425,000,000
HC Rainbow: 💎1,200,000,000
HC DM:💎5,500,000,000
What is Mrs. Claws? Mrs. Claws is a Mythical pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added on December 24, 2022.
The Dark Matter version of this pet is currently the strongest pet in the game
How much is Mrs. Claws worth in Pet Simulator X? The current Mrs.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Hardcore Pet Value List</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-hardcore-pet-value-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-hardcore-pet-value-list/</guid><description>This is our complete and up-to-date Pet Simulator X hardcore pet value list. Hardcore mode was added in Update 22, and is a complete reset of the game. Players will start from 0 in this mode and have to progress through the entire game again.
Hardcore (HC) pets used the strongest in the game. However, they were recently nerfed.
Everything in the HC world costs more and takes longer to unlock.</description></item><item><title>Rainbow Unicorn Value</title><link>/post/rainbow-unicorn-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/rainbow-unicorn-value/</guid><description>Rainbow Unicorn Value Pet Value:💎1,200,000,000
Gem Value:💎1,200,000,000
What is Rainbow Unicorn? Rainbow Unicorn is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Easter update.
How much is Rainbow Unicorn worth? The current Rainbow Unicorn value is estimated to be around 1,200,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Rainbow Unicorn? Rainbow Unicorn was available to purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Sad Cat Value</title><link>/post/sad-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sad-cat-value/</guid><description>Sad Cat Value Pet Value:💎80,000,000,000
Gem Value:💎16B
What is Sad Cat? Sad Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Steampunk Update, and is a re-skin of the Cat pet.
How much is Sad Cat worth? The current Sad Cat value is estimated to be around 80,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Sad Cat? Sad Cat was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Sea Dragon Value</title><link>/post/sea-dragon-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/sea-dragon-value/</guid><description>Sea Dragon Value (N) Pet Value:💎7,500,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎1.5B
What is Sea Dragon? Sea Dragon is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Bank Update.
How much is Sea Dragon worth? The current Sea Dragon value is estimated to be around 7,500,000,000 diamonds when traded with other pets.
How to get Sea Dragon? Sea Dragon was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Storm Agony Value</title><link>/post/storm-agony-value/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/storm-agony-value/</guid><description>Storm Agony Value Pet Value:💎270,000,000,000
Gem Value:💎270,000,000,000
What is Storm Agony? Storm Agony is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Pixel update.
How much is Storm Agony worth? The current Storm Agony value is 6,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Storm Agony? Storm Agony is obtainable for a limited amount of time by buying an Exclusive Pets Egg from the Exclusive Shop.</description></item><item><title>Capybara Value</title><link>/post/capybara-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/capybara-value/</guid><description>Capybara Value Normal Value:💎600,000,000
Golden Value:💎N/A
Rainbow Value:💎N/A
What is Capybara? Capybara is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added during the Hardcore update.
How much is Capybara worth? The current Capybara value is 600,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Capybara? Capybara can be found inside an Exclusive Egg 2. This premium egg is available to purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Gargoyle Dragon Value</title><link>/post/gargoyle-dragon-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/gargoyle-dragon-value/</guid><description>Gargoyle Dragon Value (N) Pet Value:💎2,500,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎2.5B
What is Gargoyle Dragon? Gargoyle Dragon is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Axolotl Update, and is a re-skin of both the Dragon and Demon pets.
How much is Gargoyle Dragon worth? The current Gargoyle Dragon value is estimated to be around 2,500,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Gargoyle Dragon? Gargoyle Dragon can be obtained for a limited amount of time by buying an Exclusive Pets Egg from the Exclusive Shop.</description></item><item><title>Ghoul Horse Value</title><link>/post/ghoul-horse-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/ghoul-horse-value/</guid><description>Ghoul Horse Value Normal:💎750,000,000
Golden:💎2,000,000,000
Rainbow:💎2,500,000,000
Dark Matter:💎4,000,000,000
What is Ghoul Horse Ghoul Horse is a Mythical rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X via trading.
How much is Ghoul Horse worth? The current Ghoul Horse value is estimated to be around 750,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.
How to get Ghoul Horse? Ghoul Horse was added to the game during the Halloween 2021 event. It also features in the new 2022 version as well.</description></item><item><title>Huge Axolotl Value</title><link>/post/huge-axolotl-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-axolotl-value/</guid><description>Huge Axolotl Value (N) Pet Value:💎4,200,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎275B
(G) Pet Value:💎11,500,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎550B
(R) Pet Value:💎52,500,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎2.75T
What is Huge Axolotl? Huge Axolotl is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained via trading in Pet Simulator X. It is the Huge version of the Axolotl pet.
How much is Huge Axolotl worth? The current Huge Axolotl value is estimated to be around 4,200,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.</description></item><item><title>Huge Ducky Value</title><link>/post/huge-ducky-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-ducky-value/</guid><description>Huge Ducky Value (N) Pet Value:💎700,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎75B
(G) Pet Value:💎3,300,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎215B
(R) Pet Value:💎19,500,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎850B
What is Huge Ducky? Huge Ducky is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained via trading in Pet Simulator X.
How much is Huge Ducky worth? The current Huge Ducky value is estimated to be around 700,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.
How to get Huge Ducky? Huge Ducky could only be obtained by buying the Ducky Plush from the Big Games Official Shop on August 20th, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Huge Lucky Cat Value</title><link>/post/huge-lucky-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-lucky-cat-value/</guid><description>Huge Lucky Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎560,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎60B
(G) Pet Value:💎4,700,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎270B
(R) Pet Value:💎7,550,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎400B
What is Huge Lucky Cat? Huge Lucky Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X.
How much is Huge Lucky Cat worth? The current Huge Lucky Cat value is estimated to be worth around 560,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version when trading it with other pets.</description></item><item><title>Huge Pixel Cat Value</title><link>/post/huge-pixel-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pixel-cat-value/</guid><description>Huge Pixel Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎40,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎22,000,000,000
(N) Demand: 3/10
(G) Pet Value:💎100,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎35,000,000,000
(G) Demand 5/10
(RB) Pet Value:💎850,000,000,000
(RB) Gem Value:💎90,000,000,000
(RB) Demand: 8/10
What is Huge Pixel Cat? Huge Pixel Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Pixel update.
How much is Huge Pixel Cat worth? The current Huge Pixel Cat value is 40,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.</description></item><item><title>Huge Pumpkin Cat Value</title><link>/post/huge-pumpkin-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-pumpkin-cat-value/</guid><description>Welcome to our price list for Huge Pumpkin Cat! Looking for the up-to-date Huge Pumpkin Cat value? Check out the latest prices below. We will keep this page updated daily, so always make sure to check it before you make a trade!
Huge Pumpkin Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎300,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎36,000,000,000
(N) Demand: 6/10
(G) Pet Value:💎1,200,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎105,000,000,000
(G) Demand 6/10
(RB) Pet Value:💎4,000,000,000,000
(RB) Gem Value:💎220,000,000,000</description></item><item><title>Storm Wolf Value</title><link>/post/storm-wolf-value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/storm-wolf-value/</guid><description>Storm Wolf Value Pet Value:💎480,000,000,000
Gem Value: 50,000,000,000
What is Storm Wolf? Storm Wolf is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It is one of the three “Storm” pets in the game, the others being Storm Dragon and Storm Axolotl.
How much is Storm Wolf worth? The current Storm Wolf value is estimated to be around 480,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Storm Wolf? Storm Wolf was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Dominus Astra Value</title><link>/post/dominus-astra-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/dominus-astra-value/</guid><description>Dominus Astra Value Pet Value:💎335,000,000,000
Gem Value:💎40B
What is Dominus Astra? Dominus Astra is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It has been in the game since release and is based on a limited Roblox hat also named Dominus Astra.
How much is Dominus Astra worth? The current Dominus Astra value is estimated to be around 335,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Dominus Astra? Dominus Astra was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>Hellish Axolotl Value</title><link>/post/hellish-axolotl-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/hellish-axolotl-value/</guid><description>Hellish Axolotl Value Normal:💎40,000
Golden:💎200,000
Rainbow:💎700,000
Dark Matter:💎3,200,000
HC Normal: 💎N/A
HC Golden: 💎N/A
HC Rainbow: 💎N/A
HC DM:💎N/A
What is Hellish Axolotl? Hellish Axolotl is a Mythic rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It is a re-skin of the original Axolotl pet.
It was added in the Axolotl Update and wad previously considered to be the second strongest pet in the game at one point.</description></item><item><title>Huge Santa Paws Value</title><link>/post/huge-santa-paws-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-santa-paws-value/</guid><description>Huge Santa Paws Value Normal:💎2,450,000,000,000
Golden:💎8,500,000,000,000
Rainbow:💎12,500,000,000,000
What is Huge Santa Paws? Huge Santa Paws is an Exclusive rarity pet in Pet Simulator X. It is the “Huge” version of the original Santa Paws pet. There are three different variants of it, Normal, Golden, and Rainbow.
This was the first pet ever to be purchasable with Robux.
How much is Huge Santa Paws worth? The current Huge Santa Paws value is estimated to be around 2,450,000,000,000 diamonds for the Rainbow version.</description></item><item><title>Keyboard Cat Value</title><link>/post/keyboard-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/keyboard-cat-value/</guid><description>Keyboard Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎1,100,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎1.1B
What is Keyboard Cat? Keyboard Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Glitch Update, and is a re-skin of the Cat pet while using a piano.
How much is Keyboard Cat worth? The current Keyboard Cat value is estimated to be around 1,100,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Keyboard Cat?</description></item><item><title>Nature Dragon Value</title><link>/post/nature-dragon-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/nature-dragon-value/</guid><description>Nature Dragon Value (N) Pet Value:💎2,500,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎2.5B
What is Nature Dragon? Nature Dragon is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Glitch Update.
How much is Nature Dragon worth? The current Nature Dragon value is estimated to be around 2,500,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Nature Dragon? Nature Dragon could be obtained for a limited amount of time by buying an Exclusive Pets Egg from the Exclusive Shop.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Halloween Event 2022</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-halloween-event-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-halloween-event-2022/</guid><description>The Pet Simulator X Halloween Event 2022 has arrived! This event adds new pets to the game, and spooky upgrades.
It’s likely that the event will be active until around November 11, 2022. There’s no confirmation of that yet though. Pet Simulator X Halloween Event 2022 Here are all of the features for the Halloween Event. Most of them are from the 2021 version, except new pets have been added.</description></item><item><title>Pixel Demon Value</title><link>/post/pixel-demon-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pixel-demon-value/</guid><description>Pixel Demon Value Normal:💎100,000
Golden:💎500,000
Rainbow:💎1,750,000
Dark Matter:💎8,000,000
HC Normal: 💎N/A
HC Golden: 💎N/A
HC Rainbow: 💎N/A
HC DM:💎N/A
What is Pixel Demon? Pixel Demon is a Mythical rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Pixel update.
It was previously considered the strongest pet in the game, taking the crown from Hellish Axolotl.
How much is Pixel Demon worth? The current Pixel Demon value is estimated to be worth around 8,000,000 diamonds for the Dark Matter version.</description></item><item><title>Pog Cat Value</title><link>/post/pog-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pog-cat-value/</guid><description>Pog Cat Value Normal:💎1,000,000,000
Golden:💎2,500,000,000
Rainbow:💎6,000,000,000
Dark Matter:💎6,000,000,000
What is Pog Cat? Pog Cat is a Legendary rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X via trading. It is one of the four “Pog” pets currently in the game.
How much is Pog Cat worth? The current Pog Cat value is estimated to be around 6,000,000,000 diamonds for the Dark Matter version.
How to get Pog Cat? Pog Cat was only available to obtain for one week, between September 11th and September 18th, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Storm Dragon Value</title><link>/post/storm-dragon-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/storm-dragon-value/</guid><description>Storm Dragon Value Pet Value:💎190,000,000,000
Gem Value:💎35B
What is Storm Dragon? Storm Dragon is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It is one of the three “Storm” pets in the game, the others being Storm Wolf and Storm Axolotl.
How much is Storm Dragon worth? The current Storm Dragon value is estimated to be around 190,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Storm Dragon? Storm Dragon was available for purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item><item><title>404 Demon Value</title><link>/post/404-demon-value/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/404-demon-value/</guid><description>404 Demon Value Normal:💎3,000
Golden:💎15,000
Rainbow:💎52,500
Dark Matter:💎52,500
HC Normal: 💎N/A
HC Golden: 💎N/A
HC Rainbow: 💎N/A
HC DM:💎N/A
What is 404 Demon? 404 Demon is a Mythic rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was previously one of the strongest pets in the game.
It is one of only a handful of pets to have stats over a trillion and is the only non-hacker pet that can be obtained from the Hacker Egg.</description></item><item><title>Crystal Dog Value</title><link>/post/crystal-dog-value/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/crystal-dog-value/</guid><description>Crystal Dog Value Normal Value:💎4,000,000,000
Golden Value:💎7,500,000,000
Rainbow Value:💎14,000,000,000
What is Crystal Dog? Crystal Dog is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X from Season 1 DLC Gifts.
How much is Crystal Dog worth? The current Crystal Dog value is 4,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Crystal Dog? Crystal Dog can be obtained from an Epic DLC Gift. The code for this gift can only be obtained from Mystery Pet Minifigures (4-Pack) and Mystery Toy Box Plushie.</description></item><item><title>Huge Crowned Pegasus Value</title><link>/post/huge-crowned-pegasus-value/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-crowned-pegasus-value/</guid><description>Huge Crowned Pegasus Value Normal:💎270,000,000,000,000
Golden:💎N/A
Rainbow:💎N/A
What is Huge Crowned Pegasus in Pet Simulator X? Huge Crowned Pegasus is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X.
How much is Huge Crowned Pegasus worth in PSX? The current Huge Crowned Pegasus value is around 270,000,000,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Huge Crowned Pegasus in Pet Simulator X? Huge Crowned Pegasus is a very rare pet that’s awarded to the top 10 Robux spenders in Pet Simulator X.</description></item><item><title>Huge Enchanted Deer Value</title><link>/post/huge-enchanted-deer-value/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-enchanted-deer-value/</guid><description>Huge Enchanted Deer Value (N) Pet Value:💎450,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎55B
(G) Pet Value:💎1,050,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎120B
(R) Pet Value:💎8,000,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎450B
What is Huge Enchanted Deer? Huge Enchanted Deer is an Exclusive pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X.
How much is Huge Enchanted Deer worth? The current Huge Enchanted Deer value is 450,000,000,000 diamonds for the Rainbow version.
How to get Huge Enchanted Deer? This pet is a secret, and nothing hasn’t been officially announced about it.</description></item><item><title>Huge Festive Cat Value</title><link>/post/huge-festive-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-festive-cat-value/</guid><description>Huge Festive Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎300,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎42B
(G) Pet Value:💎1,000,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎100B
(R) Pet Value:💎1,600,000,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎150B
What is Huge Festive Cat? Huge Festive Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet in Pet Simulator X. It is a re-skin of the Huge Cat, and is the Huge version of the Festive Cat. There are currently three different variants of it, Normal, Golden, and Rainbow.
How much is Huge Festive Cat worth?</description></item><item><title>Huge Hacked Cat Value</title><link>/post/huge-hacked-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-hacked-cat-value/</guid><description>Welcome to our price list for Huge Hacked Cat! Looking for the up-to-date Huge Hacked Cat value? Check out the latest prices below. We will keep this page updated daily, so always make sure to check it before you make a trade!
Huge Hacked Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎65,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎24,000,000,000
(N) Demand: 4/10
(G) Pet Value:💎320,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value:💎35,000,000,000
(G) Demand: 6/10
(RB) Pet Value:💎1,200,000,000,000
(RB) Gem Value:💎110,000,000,000</description></item><item><title>Party Cat Value</title><link>/post/party-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/party-cat-value/</guid><description>Party Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎100,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎100,000,000
(G) Pet Value:💎200,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎200,000,000
(R) Pet Value:💎300,000,000
(R) Gem Value:💎300,000,000
What is Party Cat? Party Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added during the Hardcore update.
How much is Party Cat worth? The current Party Cat value is 100,000,000 diamonds for the normal version. This pet can’t be used in the Huge-A-Tron Machine, so the value has decreased compared to other Exclusive pets.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Exclusive Pet Value List</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-exclusive-pet-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-exclusive-pet-value-list/</guid><description>Are you looking for an up-to-date Pet Simulator X Exclusive Pet value list? Well, then, you’ve come to the right place! We’ve got the prices for every Exclusive pet that’s currently been added to the game.
We will be updating this list on a regular basis, so make sure to check it before making any big trades!
Pet Simulator X Exclusive Pet Value List Updated: March 2, 2023
Adjusted pet values for many Exclusive pets.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Mythical Pet Value List</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-mythical-pet-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-mythical-pet-value-list/</guid><description>If you’re looking for an up-to-date Pet Simulator X Mythical pet value list, then you’ve come to the right place! We’ve got the prices for every Mythical pet that’s currently been added to the game.
We will be updating this list on a regular basis, so make sure to check it before making any big trade to avoid being scammed!
If you’re looking for more Roblox value lists, we also have a Pet Simulator X value list, Clicker Simulator value list, Mining Simulator 2 value list, and a Rebirth Champions X value list.</description></item><item><title>Huge Cat Value</title><link>/post/huge-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-cat-value/</guid><description>Huge Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎24,000,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎950,000,000,000
(N) Demand: 10/10
(RB) Pet Value:💎65,000,000,000,000
(RB) Gem Value:💎N/A
(RB) Demand: 10/10
What is Huge Cat? Huge Cat is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was the first “Huge” pet to be introduced into the game. There are two different variants of it, Normal and Rainbow.
How much is Huge Cat worth in Pet Simulator X?</description></item><item><title>Huge Cupcake Value</title><link>/post/huge-cupcake-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-cupcake-value/</guid><description>Welcome to our price list for Huge Cupcake! Looking for the up-to-date Huge Cupcake value? Check out the latest prices below. We will keep this page updated daily, so always make sure to check it before you make a trade!
Huge Cupcake Value (N) Pet Value:💎40,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎23,000,000,000
(N) Demand: 3/10
(G) Pet Value:💎24,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎45,000,000,000
(G) Demand 5/10
(RB) Pet Value:💎40,000,000,000
(RB) Gem Value:💎100,000,000,000
(RB) Demand: 8/10</description></item><item><title>Huge Dog Value</title><link>/post/huge-dog-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-dog-value/</guid><description>Huge Dog Value Normal:💎800,000,000,000
Golden:💎4,800,000,000,000
Rainbow: 💎40,000,000,000,000
What is Huge Dog? Huge Dog is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained via trading in Pet Simulator X. It is the Huge version of the Dog pet.
How much is Huge Dog worth? The current Huge Dog value is estimated to be around 800,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.
How to get Huge Dog? Huge Dog could only be obtained by buying the Dog Plush from the Big Games Official Shop.</description></item><item><title>Huge Dragon Value</title><link>/post/huge-dragon-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-dragon-value/</guid><description>Huge Dragon Value Normal:💎800,000,000,000
Golden:💎4,800,000,000,000
Rainbow:💎42,000,000,000,000
What is Huge Dragon? Huge Dragon is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained via trading in Pet Simulator X. It is the Huge version of the Dragon pet.
How much is Huge Dragon worth? The current Huge Dragon value is estimated to be around 800,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.
The other pet plushie that could be bought was Huge Dog.</description></item><item><title>Huge Easter Cat Value</title><link>/post/huge-easter-cat-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/huge-easter-cat-value/</guid><description>Huge Easter Cat Value (N) Pet Value:💎7,750,000,000,000
(N) Gem Value:💎320,000,000,000
(N) Demand: 6/10
(G) Pet Value:💎13,250,000,000,000
(G) Gem Value💎625,000,000,000
(G) Demand 6/10
(RB) Pet Value:💎14,000,000,000,000
(RB) Gem Value:💎800,000,000,000
(RB) Demand: 7/10
What is Huge Easter Cat? Huge Easter Cat is an Exclusive Huge rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Easter update.
How much is Huge Easter Cat worth? The current Huge Easter Cat value is estimated to be around 7,750,000,000,000 diamonds for the normal version.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Huge Pet Value List</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-huge-pet-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-huge-pet-value-list/</guid><description>Are you looking for an up-to-date Pet Simulator X Huge Pet value list? Well, then you’ve come to the right place! We’ve got the prices for every Huge pet that’s currently been added to the game.
We constantly update the values for each huge pet on this list so that you don’t get scammed.
Pet Simulator X Huge Pet Value List Updated: March 2, 2023
Adjusted pet values for many Huge pets.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Secret Pet Value List</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-secret-pet-value-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-secret-pet-value-list/</guid><description>Are you looking for an up-to-date Pet Simulator X Secret pet value list? Well, then, you’ve come to the right place! We’ve got the prices for every Secret pet that has been added to the game.
We will be updating the pet values on a regular basis, so make sure to check them before making any big trades!
Pet Simulator X Secret Pet Value List Updated: March 18, 2023
Added Kawaii World secret pet.</description></item><item><title>Pet Simulator X Value List 2023 (Hologram Update)</title><link>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-2023-hologram-update/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/pet-simulator-x-value-list-2023-hologram-update/</guid><description>Read our guide on how to get Huge Chef Cat in Pet Simulator X.
Are you looking for an up-to-date Pet Simulator X value list? You’ve come to the right page! Welcome to value town. We’ve got a complete list of all Pet Sim X pet values in a filterable, sortable, and easy-to-read list. Not only that, but we also update this page every day with new values.
We’ll constantly be updating this page with the newest pets from every update that is added to Pet Sim X.</description></item><item><title>Super Corgi Value</title><link>/post/super-corgi-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author><guid>/post/super-corgi-value/</guid><description>Super Corgi Value Pet Value:💎1,200,000,000
What is Super Corgi? Super Corgi is an Exclusive rarity pet that can be obtained in Pet Simulator X. It was added in the Easter update and is a re-skin of the Corgi pet.
How much is Super Corgi worth? The current Super Corgi value is estimated to be around 1,200,000,000 diamonds.
How to get Super Corgi? Super Corgi is available to purchase from the Exclusive shop for a limited amount of time.</description></item></channel></rss>